Welcome to the night, the car is laid out for show Star shine is so bright, watch the
secrets unfold There's magic in her hands
Whisper what the future holds
Feel the romance in every arcane lore, destined
Slipping down
Let me fix this.
I'm going to change the thumbnail
because we have a cool thumbnail.
You can check it out if you can.
And I will show it in screen, actually.
OK, that's going to be the thing.
I'll put in a thank.
Welcome to this show.
So we have names for the days now,
but I'm just going to reveal them as the days come.
So we do have Wild Car Wednesday, right?
And it's gonna be anything goes.
Let me see.
Hey, how are you guys?
Hey, what's up, Shepard?
Hold on.
I'm gonna get my glasses.
Here they are.
Anything goes, right?
It's Wild Car Wednesday.
I just want to show you the graphic I made
if you can't see it on the thumbnail.
I did get a, I did have a shower.
I like that, like my nails.
Oh, I'm already dirty.
Hopefully not.
What's up guys, hey buddy, hey buddy, hey Prairie Page.
What's up guys, but hopefully you like,
so I'm gonna make, I'm gonna really get
into this graphic design stuff,
because I think like, especially YouTube channel
really needs it, at least the thumbnails, right?
And, uh, a lot of other stuff that's, oh, hold on.
I don't know if that's the right person.
Hello? Paige?
Why is it so quiet?
Hi Paige, do you hear me?
Miss Paige? Hold on.
Paige you hear me
I don't think she can hear me
So guys who's Josh block who's this guy Josh block he's got another name. It's just a real guy
I don't know if this is a real person. Have you guys heard of this person? Okay, now I put the
new new
So this is tonight guys, this is what tonight is
Like how cool this is
Hello, not Josh block wouldn't be showing up on your stream. Okay. Yeah, so it's like some
His other name is you know, this alpha Damian, so I don't know who that might be funny
Give it a shot. It will not be funny
It'll probably be just your poor bomb, but I did want to show you this is my a graphic for tonight
So there we go. Welcome to wildcard Wednesday. It is Wednesday, right? It looks like
No, I couldn't draw that myself.
Yeah, AI didn't have that part.
It's funny how I can tell.
I mean, I'm sure we're just weeks away from me
not being able to tell what's AI,
but I could tell that's AI.
Well, because it's like so good, but...
Like the way it draws curls and stuff,
it's like only AI.
Yeah.
You know what?
Look, you're not making enough money to pay an artist.
Oh hell no, no, it's like please AI is very handy. It's actually computer humans mix with computers, which is how it's kind of supposed to be
His name is dr. Corn dog
Hi sir, nice to meet you.
You too, I hope you're having a good night.
What's the showman's name?
His name is Dr. Corndog, Dr. Corndog.
So who's his alpha?
Corndog, very nice, very nice.
Hold on a second, hold on a second, hold on a second,
hold on a second, hold on, I won't put this one.
I need to just cover it up okay, it's okay.
Oh, we got more friends?
Hello.
Friends coming on?
I'll be damned.
Hello, speaking of our verbal hold your peace.
This is Alpha Damian.
Okay, who is this?
Hello, hello out the Damian. What's up?
Going on psych. I just want to be on the why are you why are you under the name Josh block or is that you?
Look, I gave my son my computer. All right. Okay. He's a little joke
I know I don't believe okay, so you're not cammed up you don't have an icon
You have a weird name. You're getting a porn bomb. All right. All right, sir. Sir. You got all wrong. All right
Yes, show me show me yourself on camera
You want you want me turn on the camera? Yeah
I don't see anything. It's black.
It's black. No, it's not.
You have the lens cap on. I don't
know they had lens caps in the
they don't have lens cap.
lens cap.
Okay, you are okay. I was on I was on with Joe. Okay. Okay, Joe is my buddy. All right.
You referred me to your channel. Joe is your body, right? Okay. So anyway, why don't you
just hang out in the chat for a few minutes, get to know the chat, and then you can come
on the panel. Okay. I'll talk to you in a minute. Okay. Hopefully he comes back. I don't know.
and I apologize to that gentleman if I am wrong,
but that sounded like the fakest southern accent I ever heard.
And it sounded like he was laughing like.
Yeah, I know.
He was laughing a little bit.
Look at that kitty cat.
I apologize to that person, but look at that beautiful kitty cat.
Hi, Rudy.
Hi.
You just kept on brooding.
What are you doing brooding?
That's the cutest cat face.
You just got like many of the cats though.
He's a little he's a little man cat. He's probably 16 years old. He's really he looks. Yeah, he looks good for his age
Yeah, he's really super soft and like
Yeah, he's getting kind of old. I just got him this year someone was moving in
You ask him.
How many cats do you have?
Five?
Five, yeah.
But does your place smell like a litter box?
Yes or no?
No, because I have a door that goes outside.
They're mostly outdoor indoor cats.
That's good.
All of them are.
Thank you, Sweet Pete.
That's very sweet of you.
Hi, guys.
You're cats.
Yeah, Rudy's little og and see alpha Dave. Okay, alpha Davey. I just I said hey on the chat
You didn't know the chat is your but you're my fan. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know you
It was that there's a picture. That's a weird picture. It's just weird. I don't like it. You're strange
Anyway, you didn't know you're fine alpha. What are we doing?
No, it's good the guys the guys the guys whining in chat that he got cake. Okay. I just don't know you
It's like this is like, you know, you just don't walk into like, you know, Sally Jesse Raphael and have a seat next to work
conversation
Yeah, we'll have the people that have called in lately it like half of them sound like
Jeff Jets row from the Beverly Hillbillies or cleanest from the Simpsons. It's like that really exaggerated like they I don't know if it's fake
But yeah
Yeah
There's are you there's no there's no way you guys I have a six I kind of know by now like that guy's trouble
I can just tell by his voice. He wasn't like he just didn't know where he was
He's like, oh, I don't know why I'm here what I'm doing, but I'm here. I'm gonna come on the panel, right?
Okay, just talking the chat, but how's everyone tonight? It's Wednesday. It is a July 16th
I was 8 p.m. here
It's some day but we're I'm just about over the hump, right?
If you don't mind me asking, I'm in a beautiful Grand Rapids, Michigan. I'm Los Angeles. I'm a
Los Angeles. You're California boy. Nice. Just like psych. California boys. Yeah, me and psych are
about 90 minutes away from each other. Hey, he man. Hey, nobody. I should go hang out with psych.
Okay, Alpha Damian. I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I
I have a yeah
Streamers that say the n-word and stuff. I promise I mean I
Mean I've been to the Benny, but I don't know if you know Benny Blanco. He was just on the show
But yeah, I know what Benny Blanco comes on your panel. Yeah, he just came on yeah
He was on for about an hour the other night. He is one of those racist streamers. Yeah, he is he is
Yeah shadow band for doing that that very thing, but you know, he said he said the n-word about 100 times in a minute
Yeah
the
way shape or form to elicit a response to make, to get donos, you're, you're fundamentally being racist.
There's no, there's no denying it. There's no way around it.
Whoa, whoa, hold on there, fella. I, I love everyone.
Not you, no, I'm not saying you, I'm not saying you, buddy.
I love the uh.
i love the blacks the hispanics the jewish i'm not saying you i'm not saying you trevor and i
am a black hispanic so but i'm just saying bro he's young he gets drunk and he just says
i mean his full streams is it's just insane horseshit i mean yeah but i get where you're
Yeah, just like, it's just like, you know, inherent racism, which everybody is a part of.
Well, he's, yeah, he's from like the blue collar area of Pennsylvania, you know, it's kind of like a ghost town a little bit.
It's an old steel, steel, yeah.
The shithole area of Pennsylvania where every other house is fucking abandoned.
Yeah.
This is like an abandoned neighborhood. It's like he's like the only people that like living there. I think I don't see anybody there
Just walks on them. I've seen his house. Well, because yeah, he walks around his house
He looked he broadcasts from it, right? How does I have such a nice place? You know, I don't tell us
I don't want to know. It's none of my business. You have a nice
secret one of those mysteries
Yeah
I got you know, it's it's he said hey, I did clean up today. So it is like really cool. Um, it's like
feels like really good right now because it's like all organized.
I did all my like laundry and my my dishwasher running and stuff.
And so, um, do you think I do, um, I have a cup.
I haven't started tonight.
I have a.
Probably energy drink I might drink, but I have you have a couple hard harder limonies. Okay. Good. Just wondering. Yeah
You're like super new here. If you don't know that
Yeah, I've seen it on the show for a couple times in the past. We can't all be as seasoned as like Laura's you
How's our new here I am new here
I'm in my 40s, Trevor.
OK.
Well, OK.
I'm 37 today.
OK.
Oh, happy birthday.
What a great birthday.
I'm older, fatter, and more gross.
Just listen to me.
This is the way I look.
it with so it goes. Well, one thing you can do for your birthday is get better audio. That's what I
have. Yeah. There you go Trevor. It sounds like you're on an AM radio at the bottom of a trash can.
I gotta be honest with you. You seem like a great guy. You're a great guy though. I'm sorry you poor dog.
No, it's fine. I don't care.
No, you're fine. You're fine, dude. Yeah, you're fine. It's manageable. It's it's punk rock sounding, but happy breathing.
Exactly. Well, let it slide because it's your birthday. Yeah, and you do sound, you sound spunky.
Thank God.
And we got to spunking this cat too. Hey, look at the cats. Look at the cats. You see there's Lola and Trix are sleeping right there
Here we got oh, okay. Hold on. So Alpha Damien, I guess Goddison is fine. Oh, we'll see hello. Oh, he just dropped off
Well, oh
You feel like a big man
Who you feel like a big man psyche
What are you drinking today?
I've been like a big man.
You trying to cause trouble?
Siq, you stop kicking me out.
I just want to talk to my girlfriend.
I know, but you said that the...
You said the grape word last night.
I told you not to say that.
He's talking about you.
He's talking about you, Siq.
Maybe, maybe.
Trevor?
Yes, you're on the show.
Alpha, how are you?
Oh, it's crazy
We'll see where this goes. Well, he's behind me like a little
That's uh, Trevor
Look, Trevor, you're barking at me for you, brother
Yeah, corn dog. I'm all I'm gonna say is that I suggest there's other places to find panels
You can find panels on like rumble for example. I think
With that dumbass hat over that stupid headset and take your ass to another panel and I think you should take your own advice
I stream on rumble signal 66 live on rumble right now. So yes, I do
Yes, I do. Thank you very much
You see what?
He says someone said you and what's up with this corn dog guy. Yo corn dog. I don't know why I would I would remove your tattoos
All right, I'm not gonna go in the detail, but I would remove your tattoos
Let's just let's just put it like that
Your tattoos would no longer be on your body. No details. Is that your work?
No details as to how that would happen
Cheers
Yeah
SIG always wins. Thank you very much. Cheers, buddy
I'm an intelligent young man no matter what I don't believe this nigga right here is a bitch
Tell you that right now
I would I would remove the tattoos from your body without causing any harm
I'm not threatening
Now you're saying that I'm not I'm not being threatening. You're saying that it comes off weird
I'm saying weird without harm. How does that come off? We're without harm. I would remove those tattoos
I would all them tattoos on you. I will remove them without harm to you whatsoever
All right, so please explain to me how that is a threat psyche. You're just being weird
What does that mean? You know you could psyche
You know you could just say fuck you sick and I don't like you and I don't want you on my stream anymore
But instead you wait until I say something
Slightly controversial if anybody else said the same thing you would not be kicking them
He's the thing. All I'm saying is I'm gonna remove this guy's tattoos without harm with his
Now page left
Right on the moon, we're gonna be spunky him though spunky can be here in a little bit that would be happy
I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I
Sikes fan all you were drunk. I guess your husband was there
boyfriend
Yeah, you must have that vibe already that couple by the married couple by
There there's just yeah, when when someone was making fun of me or accusing me of like why don't I die?
Please please tell me your husband ain't a black man
No, he's she's not married
So boyfriend, I think he's white. I'm not sure I think maybe we're we can use what?
He's definitely very white. Okay. All right. He looks like the male version of me
Okay
Yeah, he's he's balls. He's he's beautiful. He was a mr. Clean like a young mr. Clean very very attract
Obviously put it on in a set which is fine. It's funny. I'm enjoying it
I mean as long as you feel like he's harmless sites and so be it. I don't control your pain over anything
Well, got it. Got it. Got a nose. I don't know what's so nose in the chat. So
I'm about to lose my mind on you better why don't make me go there
I don't want to do it. I don't
do it. I don't want to do it.
want to do it. I don't want to
I don't want to do it. I don't
It's monkey.
Aww.
That's sweet of you.
That's okay.
Let's get along.
How's everyone doing?
Shake hands.
Do, do, do, do, do, do.
I'm doing good.
We're doing good.
You're doing great.
Now hear your voice.
Aww.
That's very sweet.
I'm really good.
It's like, I got so much cleaning done today,
like so much cleaning.
And then like, you know,
I had a nice shower, bath,
and then I got, came on, like a clean up a little bit.
I came on when I was like all nice and organized and.
My show is kind of more organized.
I got music now.
You know, it's like you've been doing so much on the show.
Like I love the graphics.
Like I'm serious.
I'm going to get a tattoo of one of your graphics.
I'm a little for fuck's sake.
Just to use the beat of tattoo.
Yeah, OK.
Well, I got some crazy graphics in my set, but I don't.
He deserves a lot too.
I don't know if these graphics are crazy, but you know.
Yeah.
Well, I'm not going to get it on my chest.
Those are sacred.
I wouldn't touch that area, but.
Yeah, my chest is cursed.
It's not sacred, so it's just fine.
But I have a lot of tattoos on my arm,
so I think I'm going to put one.
I like that eye logo you had.
You have to post it again so I can screenshot it.
Yeah, I have tons of tattoos.
Would you ever get a name tattooed on your chest?
Yeah, I love that.
You've had a logo.
Like half a Damian?
I don't have any tattoos.
I don't have any.
Well, you should get one tonight for your birthday.
The worst tattoo I've ever seen is my dad,
my 60-year-old father.
He got this.
10 years ago, whatever he went to Vegas with his best friend, Carl.
And I swear to God, it's a Detroit Lions tattoo.
It's not a foul tattoo.
It covers his entire.
Yeah, way. And it says, you know what?
I'm going to get, I'm going to get, I'm going to get like.
I'm going to get the best idea across my belly.
Like, you know how.
Two podcast thug life. Oh, yeah. Psych awakens tarot on this. Yeah, or you can just go P. A. T. psyche awakens tarot
Just go out the Damien like oh, we have more people here guys
The studio is filling up. I don't know this guy. I don't know this guy
I don't know this guy. I don't know this guy. Wait, no, I don't know him. I do not know him.
Somehow the empty seats way more interesting than sitting in them.
Oh, that's pretty safe. I don't know that guy. Forget it.
Why you put that up right there? What's going on? I don't know this guy.
Because I had someone backstage. Who's this Danny person? Or who's this?
Who is the person backstage named Danny? Are you there? Danny, are you there? Hello.
Where's daddy? How are you, sir?
Where's daddy?
And the reason I know who he is, his name's Miley, baby.
And the reason I know who he is
is because of his superb etiquette
in regards to muting himself when he's not talking.
Look at that kitty cat, psyche.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, look at that beautiful cat, everybody.
You're so beautiful.
That's real cute.
Ignore him.
That's a good-ass cat right there.
That's a real cat.
Ooh, sorry, he's stepping on a cute one.
Wait, Trevor, Trevor, what are you talking about, Zach?
My mind's a little hazy.
You know what I'm talking about.
Billy Blue?
You know what I'm talking about, buddy.
Bonnie Blue?
I don't know what he's talking about.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Betty blue is a great French
Betty blue
Oh look at the Siamese is a Siamese
Yeah, it's psyche. Did you see my kids like to interrupt me? So I gotta meet Superman
Superman is there a new Superman movie or there is you should go down to the mall
Now, you should go down to the Suncoast Plaza or whatever it's called and go see the new Superman movie and get high against someone else.
I haven't been to the movies. I think the last one I saw was Great Gatsby 2012.
Wow, that was a long time ago.
In the theater. In the theater, yeah.
You should go to the movies. It's fun.
Bunky, do you really have a boyfriend?
She does. Hold on. I'll fix this.
I really do.
Remember how he designed these cats to think duck sauce. Oh god, you're supposed to eat cats. Okay. Oh, look at the kitty cat
Yeah, no cats
Hi kitty, what's the cat's name? Oh, he likes me bixie bixie bixie bixie bixie. How are you doing binks?
Like Jar Jar Binks is that your favorite Star Wars character? No, it was from the um that the Sanderson sisters movie now
I'm having like a fire but I hope it's focus focus focus. Yeah. Oh, yeah
Yeah, okay cute name. Yeah, I had a half-slam used cat Chuck Stegall's cat is named was named Salem after
Sabrina the Teenage Witch but
Yeah, I lost another chuck and lost another cat. It's like three cats. And I had a kid named Salem that ran away to
Yes, yes
Well, yeah, he's you're sitting right with them, right? It's like you just don't know what it's not to like talk
Okay, just say hi. All right. Yeah
Parents with some so it's fine
Hello
Hello, how are you?
I'm I'm good
Okay, how old are you sir?
I'm only 16. Okay. Oh
Yeah
I gotta go then psyche if you're gonna have no his father's on the phone
It's his father's right there. I'm right here. I'm right here. Psych
Okay, okay, well that we said hi we said hi, that's fine. Okay, I was it wasn't up. He wants to tell oh
Okay, what do you want to say? What do you want to ask? Okay?
Well, it's obviously the same person.
It's Billy Blue.
OK, it's Billy Blue.
Guys.
I was on the panel with this guy.
I know who he is.
and he was a gentleman. He was an absolute gentleman. And the reason I know who he is is
because of his etiquette. He always moots himself when he's not talking. He has superb etiquette
when it comes to that. But I think his name was Michael or something like that.
And they're like, Oh, Billy Blue was like, Oh, Michael was saying this and that about the the the Middle Eastern students.
And I'm like, Michael said that because he sounded like a pretty good guy.
When I was in pain, I was like, Daddy, what's the meaning?
I know who you are, I know who you are, young man.
I know who you are, young man.
So you're the same voice.
You are your own son.
Look, I don't know.
The Bonnie Blue, all right.
I'll not know Michael's look.
He said Billy Blue.
I just stabilized Chayette.
Billy Blue gave me.
I don't think my son should have to listen to this.
OK, well, hang up on us.
Maybe it's not the show for you.
OK, go away.
I can go to the other room daddy
Okay, this is just too weird guys are being too weird. Go okay. Go away. You're too weird. Yeah, that's super weird
It's the same person
How are you Sparky? It's nice to meet you. I'm a Trevor. Hi Trevor. Did I hear it was your birthday?
37 guys
Happy birthday
Yeah. Yeah. I'm another day older and I'm another day fatter is basically how it goes at this age.
But where are you from? If you don't mind me asking, I always ask everyone. I'm in beautiful Grand Rapids, Michigan.
Oh, I'm in California.
A lot of people in California. Okay. Oh, I hear the accent. That's so cute
Yeah, you did you pull the you pull the Midwest gosh darn
Yeah
Well, happy birthday, I hope you're having a great day
Oh, I'm drunk. I'm drunk. So that's good.
It's going good.
That is good.
How was your day going?
Go ahead.
I had a stay off from work, but it was like super productive.
That's cool.
Awesome. Awesome.
Yeah.
I got a lot of stuff done and I'm,
I had a lot of good things that I've been waiting for for a long
time come through for me.
Don't step on the keyboard.
And I'm like really relieved and so happy.
So happy.
Very nice.
Yeah.
I know this is a hard, I'm 37.
I said that.
I know this is a hard question to ask.
I'm 40.
Oh, are you really?
Yeah.
All righty. All righty. Do you have cats too? Was that a cat that just came in?
That was a cat. That was big.
How many do you have?
Two. And I have four dogs.
Oh, yes. You okay? Okay.
Yeah.
Are you black psych? Are you back, buddy?
Miley.
Oh, I got you.
I'm here.
Miley.
Okay.
Come here.
Yo, is that mad daddy or what?
Who?
Trevor Ryan sounds like mad daddy moonshine
That's not a dog there. That's a dog. Oh
She's the thing of the multi poo. Yeah, this one's like the mini golden doodle and then the white one is the multi
poo this one's like
Kind of like Fawzi Christine's dog
Hey Trevor pal, I heard it was your birthday buddy. Thank you
Happy birthday pal. I got you something. I got you a gift
Well, he got me he's gonna pull his middle finger out of his pocket
The one page made what does that say? Oh, you got his actual birthday name on it
Real names blue flowers. I love this blue roses
That's the way just do you buddy
It's Canada dry
Are you having a good night?
What about who?
He farted in Paige's chat room earlier.
Yeah, I knew that all the time.
He came in and I stank bombed it up.
Oh, one time he made a weird sound.
He was like moaned on the stream.
And we're like, what was that?
And we didn't know if he was on the toilet or what.
They were just a really, really weird sound.
Yeah, he's got some digestive issues online.
Or maybe I don't have digestive issues.
Maybe I'm pretty regular.
That's good.
How are you, sir? How are you? I'm trying to talk to you as a human, one-on-one,
stop the nonsense, the gimmick, or whatever. How are you, sir? Who? How are you? Are you good?
Me? You, sir? Yes, yes, indeed. Yeah, I'm doing good. I'm doing good.
See, see, this is the type of guy he can't have a conversation.
It's just the gimmick.
I know, I know, I know, I know.
He can not have any conversation.
Maybe he communicates their gas.
Would you like a moment to relieve yourself?
Maybe you'll feel better.
Yay!
That was crazy, bro.
That was wild.
For some people it's all about dick and fart jokes, you know, that's how you relate and communicate.
It's crazy how you can have a one-on-one conversation with somebody who's willing to be a human instead of a gimmick.
and, you know, just have a friendly conversation.
And then there's these Zoomers,
these Zoomer Fox who just think they're funny and smart
and it's all a gimmick.
It's all a mind gimmick.
A cock-a-mind gimmick.
Buddy, how old do you think I am?
consumer. I don't care how old you are. You act like you're 16. There's something in your head.
Bro, are you upset right now? Are you talking about me or him?
Oh my God, Sweet Pea, don't give him any ideas. Goddy, do you see what you're telling the chat now?
Are you upset right now, Goddy?
What happened?
Gotti's not upset.
Gotti doesn't sweat.
I'm sorry.
Idiots like you.
I'm not paying attention.
What's going on?
What else is new?
Huh?
Who's there?
What?
Oh, my God.
The dementia is setting in.
Where am I?
Yeah.
Can you imagine trying to have a conversation with introduce yourself to somebody who's a human and this stupid mother fucker just wants to play games?
I have a 16 year old. I can completely, completely understand me.
You're not funny. You're not intelligent.
God, it seems like you're playing the games right now, buddy.
You're a fucking asshole.
talk to Gotti. Why can't I talk to Alex McQueen? Why can't I talk to all these people on panel
and they can have a human conversation? But for some reason you, you, you think you're so funny
and you think you're so smart with your gimmick, but you're just a fucking asshole is what it comes
I don't even know what the fuck you're talking about.
Trevor, I love you, Trevor, you're perfect for me.
Trevor, don't ruin your birthday on this.
I know, I thought he was not having a good time.
Oh, I don't care about my birthday, Sam.
I do.
Trevor's having fun.
He loves his stuff.
Nobody who comes on this panel, I get it.
They're all trying to get a rise out of everybody and
be humans and cause trouble.
But it's like if I say, hey man, what's up man?
Are you having a good day?
And everyone, like I said, Gotti, Alexander McQueen,
all these people I've been on panel with.
And then there's this one stupid asshole
who thinks he's funny with his stupid fucking gimmick.
You can't be a human.
You can't be a human and have a conversation.
What's this gimmick?
What is my gimmick?
What's my gimmick, bro?
The camera driving?
I think his gimmick is talking about my non-existent gimmick. What's my gimmick?
I don't know Don. You really put it like not in his underwear.
You're stupid as fuck. You're stupid as fuck. So when I say how is your day?
Hi, sir. I'm Trevor. I want to introduce myself. How is your day? Why do you have to turn that into a
some fucking horse shit and try to be funny. You think you're funny. You're not funny. You've
never been funny a day in your life. You've never been funny a day in your life. So why can't you
have a human conversation? That's what I want to ask you, motherfucker. Stupid bitch. Stupid bitch.
Oh my god. Boo-Boo, you can't hear this language.
Love you Trevor. It's okay Trevor. Don't don't let it get to you man. You know, that's all they want
Do you do hard drums, dude
No, fuck you look at this, look at this fuck you look at this.
Why do you have a picture of my dog?
What about you asshole?
Oh my god.
Do you have a whole file of like screenshots of my panels?
You like stalk me.
I know everything about you.
Do you know his name?
Yeah, Charlie.
Oh my god, you do.
Am I wrong?
Is it really Charlie?
Yeah.
Oh, wow.
If somebody comes on the panel.
It's Charleston, but we call him Charlie.
I fucking totally made that up.
No, that's hilarious.
Wow.
It's Charleston and Bartholomew.
Who's the psychic now?
Yeah, I got EG's.
You need to go like guess the lottery numbers.
All right. All right. Well, well, thank you guys. Thank you for having us like it was nice to talk to you.
Hey Trevor, enjoy the rest of your night, man.
Yeah, Trevor. Happy birthday, honey.
Yeah, don't let him bother you, Trevor.
Don't let him bother you, man.
dry is that what you go by? I try to be cool to you. You came on the panel and I try to
talk to you as a person. And this is an example of all you assholes on IP2 who think you're
funny with your stupid fucking gimmicks. I try to be a human to you, motherfucker.
Catch me on an IP2. Listen to Trevor go here. Is he an IP2 guy? I don't even know.
No. Yeah, man. I'm a big IP2 guy. Yo, Trevor.
Keep it on ice buddy. Keep it on guys guys. He's not chicken Andy. He looks like him, but he's not him. Okay. Oh my god
It's okay, it went perfect for me
Anyway, Charlie call him Goddy call him
You wanna come say hi come say hi to Goddy get your ass over you flea mongrel
He's huge too. Oh
Look at him. Oh, look, you're gonna be so happy
You know why cuz you taste like alpaca
It's not a nice thing to say little baby
Okay, hold on. I signed up for Tiktok today.
What do you need justice for? Tiktok, huh?
Well, I mean, it's like...
Oh, jeez, bless you.
Emma was on Tiktok before she was on YouTube, and she had 23,000 subscribers, and she got...
She got banned, you know, she got because she broke a few rules of it and so she went to YouTube
But and so I want to try to do tiktok maybe and like just see if I can get it to work
But there's people there's one thing though. Yeah, I can dance, but there's one lady that is on
On tiktok. She makes I think half a million dollars a year
She basically goes into a store like she pretends to be a vegan and that goes into like meat restaurants
But she's not really a vegan and she like looks kind of weird, but she goes in like wearing
Baggy pants and boxer shorts and like cow cow boxers, and then she goes in and she goes shaking my giat at this people
Her giat or whatever
Yeah, yeah, and she makes like half a million dollars a year by doing that
Yeah, and that's literally all she does that's literally all she does
You don't have a gimmick. I haven't I don't need a gimmick. I mean it's like gimmicks are
Well, you know, whatever it's like there was like no, it was like your gimmick. Yeah, he was provoked by your gimmick
I don't even know what my gimmick is. I don't either. He got so so upset
I've never seen someone go from happy to like miserable so quickly
It's because he picked up on Canada's right energy. He doesn't know him
He just said he said one thing to him and he just got his answer. He didn't like, you know, just like
Good thing. I was bubbly to him. Otherwise, I would have my
Uh
You can't a dry don't you you and him? Oh, yeah. Well, you know just be yourself. You know be yourself
Okay, anyway, so
Okay, that was what my tablet wasn't working on
He's not around now is that his house lucky you
Today was his dad's birthday, so he had to go down there, and I had a whole bunch of nice. I had a bunch of mongo stuff
I had to do
Did you meet his parents? Oh, yeah a long time ago. Oh, they like you and everything? Yep. That's good. Yeah
Well, yeah, you don't want to be the you don't want to be barking
That's my cat!
That's your cat?
I thought Gotti had a dog. That's why I wanted to know.
The dogs, there's a really loud dog barking out here outside.
Wow.
Actually, I could hear how it sounds on the camera.
It sounds really loud, but it's actually far away.
That's funny how echoes and mics do weird things.
Yeah, because I came I can barely hear the dog, but it's pretty loud on my mics when it comes on
Let's see. So, how are we doing guys? So I have my stuff to charge up. Okay there there
I'm thinking about some some stuff about the show. I'm a random guy. I mean, this is
I don't know why you let me on here, dude. It's like
A great gimmick man, I can't even fucking. What's up
The gold Rolex, that's his gimmicks, you know what? I can't even compare with this guy
Funny guy fuck dude. See I killed the stream. That's what I did. I killed the channel
No, you didn't kill the channel
It's like actually protected by aliens and
Won't be going down absolutely fine. Hey, yeah, the Rolex guy. It's a Rolex guy. What's up? Yeah, and you know some aliens are cute
Some are not so cute
I wouldn't be myself man, but you always boot me off. You always boot me off the channel when I'm when I'm being myself
You know, it was it was Canada dry
No, no, that's when you said the n-word and stuff. I don't like that. I say all kinds of words like
Yeah, I'm being myself
I feel I feel very censored here, but so I do kind of tone it down a little bit. What is you?
I mean, it's like I say I'm censored. I'm censored by it. I'm censored by it. I'm a fucking red
I love rednecks. I mean, I'm not really redneck, but yeah, kind of you might be a redneck
You're not redneck, I don't know not really kind of who knows
You know, yeah, well, I say you don't sound like Jeff Fox worthy. I mean, we actually had a couple people that like you know, sound like you sound like, you know
Cletus good times. Yeah good times. I mean he wears suspenders
Yeah, he's oh, yeah, I mean, it's like he's in that shit deep that fell off the turnip truck or something like that
I don't think I've ever worn suspenders
What are they?
Overalls they're called overalls. Yeah, dude. That's crazy
maybe
Overalls with no shirt. I don't know if you were wearing underwear under there either, but you think that's is that
He's just free ballin
This chick is like he's like a little old man little like an innocent like little hillbilly like you know like you know
It's just like I'm I'm harmless. I'm harmless and then he's like
He's scary sometimes. Why what do you do sparky around girls? He you're I can't address
Very loud many times and on my stream. We did it too. You're not allowed to bring them on live stream
Do I never brought them on your stream? I know I know but I'm saying I'm just saying I'm just right. Yes
There's an algorithm that picks it up. Yes, but he he um he did it
He put guns on my stream and then so did Alex and so did
Road nomad. I mean it's like a lot of
N words
I just bring the dogs out.
Picture TV.
Picture TV Canada, it was too loud.
We're trying to have a conversation here,
not listen to like.
I don't even know what you heard.
I heard some other voice and it wasn't anybody
that was on the panel, so.
As soon as I took you off, it was gone.
So there was another voice in the background
and I got kicked out?
Yep.
Yeah, your audio was kind of shitty.
It sounds better now.
It does.
Yeah.
You could have just said something's going on with your audio
Why do you keep correcting me?
And uh, you're on the show like what are you complaining? I like are you right back on? You know, I just trying to be more positive
Conversation, you're not you don't really listen. You don't really respond on time and stuff like that. So, you know
It's not really helping with my positivity either. So he's really not helping. Yeah
I'm a little much, you know
Okay, well
I will give you the nudge
Give anything to say
Any last words to sketch you on dawn, you know, what this is I said any words to sketch you on die
You just so you're just so you're so annoyed by everything makes me a
No, I'm just confused what you guys are
Okay, well, I don't know you remember you were on last night, you know, I let you on for like several hours last night
You showed that your watch collection for about an hour and
You know what I didn't like Pat
He was doing wash talks so I hopped in there. I know how to do so a little I mean
I'm kind of new to the lobby about a couple of two years maybe and
He calls my watch a submarine or he mispronounces it number one
Guys guys like is it fake? I'm like, why are you gonna ask me if my watch is fake dude? Like I'm like I'm out of here
Of course, it's not still disrespect
But then he was like saying yesterday's like oh well you can like he's like oh, you know the big businessman
You know, but they all they do is look at you don't make any if you make less if you make like a hundred K or less
A year and you have a thirty five thousand twenty five thousand on our watch. You're just a poser like what the fuck is that?
Yeah, I mean if we want to have a nice watch and they make a hundred K let them have it
Who's he just fucking he got a bunch of shitters. Hey Canadian guy. You got a bunch of shitter watches. That's what you got
Okay shitters
Did you ever get the garbage peel kid on tear cards? No, I didn't he could he didn't check win with me about it
I'm not sure if he I don't know robot. I'm just still learning. I'm like, I still I still like I just feel bad when people come back
And I'm like, okay, I'll include them even though he annoyed me last night and stuff
I still let him back and then he's just a whiner. He's a whiner. It's a why are you taking what?
It's weird energy
Yeah, I know and I'm very like sensitive to negative energy too. It's why I can get listen guys
I'm gonna go get some food. I'm gonna burn some incense. If like if my move gets a little back to normal
I'll hop back on I'm just trying to stay positive. It's been a hard work day. That's all I get a little grouchy, okay?
You weren't grouchy. I think you're a wonderful. I feel like I'm grouchy, but I'm tired
Happy honey, have a good day
So I want to buy you something psyche on your wishlist. What's the number one thing you want?
I was gonna buy you those cards that that person backed out on it. So I
Want to treat you. Oh, thank you so much. You're so sweet. Yeah, you can send me a link in the back chat of what you want the most
Okay
You know, I'm always like, you know, I've got I gotta I think there's some cats cats stuff on there
Or there's a you know, there's a few there's a few decks of cards. I don't have damage stuff on there
Pick your favorite thing and then just send me the link in the back chat and I'll get it right now.
Oh, you're so sweet. Oh my god. You always bring so much like happiness to me like you and I really appreciate it.
Oh, I appreciate you too. You know you you're up. I remember like when I was like all freaking out a couple weeks ago like at all
when everyone was mad at me and stuff and then
uh, I felt like I felt like I was being trolled and then you came on and you were like so, um
Just like you made everything better.
I don't know, it's just like, it was like.
You do, like sometimes I have really, really hard days
at work and then, you know, I'll keep you on.
Like when I'm coming in and out of my rooms and stuff,
I'm actually gonna cry about it a little bit.
But it's been like really like hard at work
and then I come in there for a little bit
and I'm like relieved.
So it's really nice.
Aw, that makes me feel really good.
I'm like, I'm so happy to be like,
you know, a positive force in people's lives
and somebody that they like enjoyed listening to
and they said, thank you so much.
Yeah, it just makes the day go back so much easier
and so much better.
And when you like walk out of like some really bad
negative energy and then like you come in
and I see you doing goofy stuff or just being positive
or just like reading stuff, I don't know.
Some of it is like this like coincidentally timed stuff
that is so comforting and it's so nice.
So.
Oh, thank you. Yeah. Yeah, that's what I really I try to really try to go by like
Intuition on this show, but it's like and I and not also like
I'm kind of getting like I had the drama part of the show and the tarot all like
Separated right they should have been together. They should have been like I should be like reading cards on the energy of the chat
Yeah, like when someone's issues you can pull up. Yeah, be like here. Let me see what's really wrong with you
Like what's driving this negative energy? Yes, sorry. I turned my cam off. I started crying and anyone okay, okay?
yeah it's just like one of those like do you know when you go through a whole bunch of bad stuff
and then like it finally works out you know yes as much as it can and like everything has worked
out and i'm so relieved and it's like making me cry i think
Yeah, well, I just really like I've felt like everything's gonna be fucked up before and then it's like I think a page and be to talk to me
But they're like, you know, there's something called the law of attraction like, you know, there's not at the station
I like they're like you just have to think you know think positive things and you know
Believe in yourself and she's like the miracles they happen and then actually it did like the miracle did happen
So yeah, it's really true. I mean I I
you can tell that I like live my life just trying to be positive and like spreading kindness as much
as I can you know don't don't get me wrong I have the other side you've seen it too but um I think
what you put into the world you attract back to you and I think if more people live by that things
would be so much better for everyone so yeah yeah especially like you know it's like if you put you
know love out into the world you know and it's even especially if you're not not not expecting
Um, like it does come back to you like the positive things come back to you when you're nice to people
It comes just like remember like it's like you're never like really like you're doing something nice for people
It's like it's not really like sacrifice. It's like, you know
It'll benefit everybody. It's like, you know, like um, it's just good energy into the universe, right? Something's in the air
What do you feel you feel something weird or fucking low key or something? Yeah, what is it looking?
I feel pretty good today
I think things are shifting changing like you feel that like it's almost like
You know in a stuffy room or someone like open the door down the hallway
And like there's just a little bit of fresh air coming in and like things are lifting getting better
Yeah
And that's funny because I just like, you know, I just like did my dishes and like, you know, clean up some laundry and clean up a little bit and got all this, you know, got things kind of smelling good around here.
And it's like, it just does like, you know, when you clean your environment around you, like have an organized environment, you feel so much better.
Oh, I feel like my thoughts get organized better when my environments, the cleanest it can be to like just everything feels tidy, you know.
It's like as above so below, you know, it's like, you know, so that's the same thing, you know, so if like something is not going right inside then, you know, maybe
You're not fixing it, you know, try something on the outside and like, you know, try to try this then it might
Manifest on the inside right yeah, and then the yeah and so on and so forth well
I kind of thought like I never believed in manifesting things, but I really tried to overhaul my thoughts and
Like just energy in the past year
I would say probably since I've been with Justin
I would say like a year and a half and it is working like it is it is insanely working
and so many good things are happening and like the harder I work and the
better I am that the just everything keeps falling into my lap and like working out and it's really amazing
Awesome. Yeah, it's like, you know, I think that, you know, we'll continue just to be, you know, blessed
Because well, you know, I know that, you know, you go out there with like a pure heart and
You know good. I think
You know people that do good in the world deserve good things
Everybody here. Yeah, I hope everybody has something amazing happen to them today
Yes, and it's like and everybody has to like every like there really are every day. There's gifts. There's miracles
There's every day. There's like opportunity. There's like, you know, even if it's just you, you know, you're doing something for yourself
You know, sometimes you have to make it happen for yourself, too
And there's nothing wrong with that. There's nothing wrong with loving yourself and like doing something nice for yourself like taking yourself on a date
Even if it's something as simple as just like, you know,
hanging out at home and taking a bubble bath
and getting your favorite food
and romancing yourself a little bit.
When the world doesn't want to be nice to you,
you can start the niceness yourself.
Right it starts with it and it's like also it's everything starts with like you know you the individual because it's like it really is art
Like every every individual is like their own world. It's like they have their own perspective of the world
It's like in different worlds and everybody's mind, right? It's all the same world, but and so
Yeah, it's like if you change if you change yourself you can change the world because we are we are the world in a way
Okay, I'm looking at your Amazon list. Okay, well because I was looking at I was like I like the cat stuff
I'd like a few of the decks. I don't have that much stuff on it
You know, so whatever whatever whatever strikes you because how about I get the cat something and I get you something
How about this cute food bowl?
Yes
For the cats because he doesn't love food, right? And then let's look for you
I have
Did they buy the garbage mail kids thing? I don't know. I don't know but I think I mean he was he was you know
He's very like, you know, I admit that he's going to but I know I don't want to get it if you're gonna
Let me see if I'm gonna still get it trying to think of it like if there's a yeah, you know always come across really cool decks
You know, I wish I wish they had filled the golden girls one
But you know that's that I guess pick a cool deck and then you have to pull me the first card from it
Okay, yes, you got it. You got it. I
Will yeah, there's a lot of really cool. I'm thinking of like there's this deck that has like kind of like
It's kind of got a criminal kind of criminal twist to it. It's like
Oh guys, I got this like this from my tablet to like this like K. This is really good
Oh, let me see. I was in this I was in the wish list. Let me see. It's a clear case. See this. Oh, that's cool
Yeah, yeah, very classic
Yeah
So this is okay, so I'm gonna look in the Amazon. Let me see
Yeah, Amazon is all in this tablet.
Is it the Darkseid Skeleton Terra deck?
Maybe, let me see.
It's like this one deck that is,
oh, here it is, I see it.
It's called the Soul Me True Crime Clues Oracle cards.
Conspiracy Oracle deck, 80 card Oracle.
I'll put it, I'll put it,
or that's actually, okay, there's this one
or there's another one.
Let me see what it is.
I like that, let me see.
Except that it's the same, I think.
Okay, so one's called shoe crime oracle cards and the other were Carl are called
Let me see I
Don't see it on your list. Oh, yeah, I'm putting it on right now. Oh you're putting it on right now. Okay. I'll refresh
Let me see. This is my freaking. Okay. It's a little bit slow. Here we go. Okay. I'll put this one add to this
Okay wish this
Okay, that's on and you can see they're gonna be that one or it's gonna be the one under it because it's like let me see
So whatever you like, whatever you think
I'll put those on I think
They're kind of they look pretty cool. Yeah, I'm spreading
Yeah, legal proceedings
True crime. I'm good. Is there?
Okay, well
My apps frozen anyway, but yeah, I mean that looks pretty cool
That's right tastes better than ginger. I like the taste of ginger election better than Sprite
What do you guys think you bad energy sucks you hate bad?
Well, the thing with bad energy is energy is energy too, right bad energy can maybe feel heavier. It can feel
Chaotic, but you can transmute energy. You can take you can take in negative energy
And you can turn it into light actually can turn it into light easier than it is just turning like light energy to light, right?
It's uh
Yeah, so it's very different things, but sure. Oh, yeah, they are different. What is the flavor and ginger is ginger?
Yeah, but it's it's not really potent. I don't like the taste of true ginger, but I like ginger ale
Yeah, that'd be spicy, but it would be spicy, but yeah, I do love ginger ale
Yeah, I had a ginger it was it was in a
It was Chinese themed and it was a ginger Rita and it was the worst thing I ever had in my life
I thought oh, I like ginger ale so I like a ginger margarita. No way. That was terrible
Ginger is so spicy
Mmm. Yeah, I'm not really into the spicy drink, so my dad always loved a good Bloody Mary.
Like, you know, that has Sebastian going in, so.
Nah, I don't, I don't know.
I really don't even like very much heart alcohol.
Okay, so Sigg wants to say hi. Okay, hold on.
I only see the true crime cards.
Sigg, the other one didn't come along.
That's crazy.
Okay, I'm looking at it.
Oh, sorry, babe.
Not resting.
No, it's crazy.
I was, I, uh.
You know, Psyche, have you seen that guy?
Have you seen that guy that he literally has like a toilet seat?
And when I, when I buy a box, it'll just go straight to you, right?
Like, I don't have to do anything weird.
Okay.
Yep. Yep.
What's up? What's up? Say, um, have you seen that guy that wears a toilet seat?
I'm not interested in guys who work for the team, it sounds pretty disgusting.
No, I'm serious. No, no, no. I mean, uh, that dude, I'm just saying.
I don't know, I haven't heard of him. Wait, what's his name?
Motion Man.
Okay, so you're why do you want me you want me to talk to me?
You want me to talk about some guy with a toilet on his head? It's what what what say what bro?
I'm just looking bro. I was just looking at his life. So I have 1.6 milli
What are you trying to say?
Point what's the point? I was looking at that. What do you mean? What's that point?
It's like you have a lot of points to make but when I make my points, bro
You don't like it and you take me out. So don't be asking me for no points, right?
I'll ask you for whatever I want
No, you won't yes, I will facts my yeah facts. I will
Whatever I want a spunky at the other the other deck looks kind of like better. I don't know you can have a look and see what
Okay, I'll put it on I'm evil. I put it on the list. Okay, let me refresh it Oliver. Jabrona you get no pussy
Oh, yeah. And that's literally psyche.
I mean, sorry, Oliver Gibroni.
That's literally that's me saying that.
Oliver Gibroni, you get no pussy telling you that right now.
That's just crazy, bro.
This is sad. It's tragic. It's tragic for you, my guy.
Okay, so Paige hangs out here. She was here just early the night school the school bathrooms hangs out here sometimes
You know he still does 420 hangs out here sometimes and summer and hangs out here sometimes and Vinnie
I don't know. I've seen Vinnie once in a while too. So rebuke is crazy. What does that even mean? What is psyche?
What does rebuke mean?
Other people say that it is a return to sender.
Yeah, it's like return to sender.
I send it back to you, send it away, send it away, right?
Oh, shit.
Well, there's a difference.
There's a difference between review or sorry,
there's a difference in return to sender and just like return.
Yeah.
Well return to senders I can't send the energy back rebuke. I mean I feel like return return to sender is more negative
Like I feel like you can say this negative energy is coming towards me and I just I'm deflecting it right you could say
Right, I got hypothetically right. I don't um whatever right you could say I'm deflecting it
But then to say I'm gonna deflect it and I want it to go back to you. That seems negative
Well, it's his return to senders like sending the energy back to his origin and it kind of like and so it's like
You know, someone's gonna send it out. They why can't they have it sent back to them?
It's we already sure they mean sent back sent back to the Amazon
But I mean at the same time though, like, you know, they say they say love
Thyself as a neighbor or whatever right and like and
Forgiveness and all that they may be neighbors and honestly, I believe that for the most part
I'm not gonna say I've never had a
Projectile device pointed at somebody's head by my own self before I'm not gonna say that but I do I agree with what you're saying
Okay
Yeah, so cheers it's cheers, you know, and it's they can see
And I don't hate you say and I you know, I don't hate you either
I it's looks like yeah, I said that I don't like you and I stand by that
But and then you took that like as if like I hate you
You know what I mean like I just like I don't like lying to people
I don't like acting like like like like again. I don't want to sound negative towards you, but I
Let me just not say it right for the sake of diplomacy as as I'm sure you would like
Do whatever you want
The thing is that if I if I start saying these things and you just kick me out
Right, so I will I mean we'll there's if there's slanderers or something like that or if they're like no
No, none of the things that I I try my best to not say anything that is slanderous or
Fictitious or false in any way. I try my best to maintain them. Yeah. Yeah, we all should
Yeah, and that's why that's why you're like you're like looking at that red button and you're like
This guy out soon. That's why but if you're no
I will if you say something that I don't like but it's like a guy word or I bet it's like the thing is
I mean the thing the thing is that it's sort of like you ever been to the hospital
Where they have that like you see where they show the the sliding they have a sliding patient scale
Or like like you can if you if you don't have a certain amount of money
Yeah, they'll charge you less
We're seeing that
Mm-hmm. So it's like it's sort of this thing where it's like
It's a sliding scale if you imagine an abacus as for what is acceptable and what isn't
Okay, so that's why I'm just saying what I'm saying
OK, I guess Nick winner left.
Is it frustrating, psyche?
Is it frustrating for you to say, OK, like more times than before?
Because you you only said OK and like every so often with Nick.
I guess with me, you have to say more often.
There's a little bit more of an active conversation.
Yeah, I mean shout out shout out to Nick Nick's next cool guy
He was literally Nick already TV is I'm ready TV's and I'm shooting there
And yeah, I know that machine gun on the street
Nothing against Nick, but yeah, you're like mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. You're literally like
Well, because he was just it was like it was like he was not in a conversation. He was talking at me
He was talking at me and he was saying stuff that was kind of dumb and like, okay, what is this point?
That's how I want to know what's the point
What but what do they mean and not what are they saying right?
But and nope, here's the thing though my point as you're referring to right now is that he had no point
He had no point.
Yeah. There was nothing that he was saying and yet and yet I was joining
attempting to join several times with several things to discuss.
That being said, objectionable to you.
But several things to discuss, but you're but but you're there.
I'm just I was just I was just doing my interrogation thing. I was just questioning, right? No, it's interrogation. You asked people you don't
I was asking him questions. He was like that. He was like just like talking at me
He was very very stoned and uh, I'm not the main takeover. I mean this question. Yeah, I just let him talk
What you have a problem with my interview style like I was like if he was saying something interesting
I could like throw back at him. I could say it, but I couldn't there's nothing interesting to say
He was just talking about nonsense and then he was like, oh well
I can't talk about how we're allowed to do secret things with these deer like, you know
Kill them with assault rifles and down the public street like what okay. Well, what is the like why?
Is that legal? I've never even heard about that, but I guess
You've never been a content oversea you your panel barnacle some eat has created
Okay, well, here's the thing psyche. There's like a lot of other messages that you didn't read
Okay, you know what I mean what like what messages?
Like literally
Larry of other messages
Surrounded by that message that you haven't read. So at what point is you reading that comment? Is that an endorsement?
No, I was no because there's other there's other there's other comments
And that's a one or two. It's a flurry of
Other comments right here that you can see that you have not read
I know but I'm gonna try I go back to the comments sometimes and I just read with others on the screen and then it's like sometimes
They're long and then I get to a point and I like oh, you shouldn't be saying that so I don't endorse
Well, that was a particularly long comment. That was um
If you look at this string here, that's at least three three lines of text
So it's it's a long comment enough for you to have to discern
He's rambling. He's rambling. He's rambling. Say he on a positive note. It's enough for you to have to discern
Everyone, do you hear me?
Yeah.
You know, I really like to have a conversation with that kid,
Sig, because I've seen him when he's not wasted off his ass.
And he is a really articulate and funny young guy,
but when he's drunk, I mean, it's just, I mean,
just what you see there is just complete rambling
about nonsense, but I guess that's all of us.
When we get wasted, but I'm just he was drinking this morning at like when I was here at like four in the morning
So I mean started so it's like oh boy
That's it. That's him always though, so
I mean
I just against anyone whoever I had a
an incident was
That was you know, I don't hold grudges. It's it's whatever it's it's all fucking it's all fucking horseshit
Holding and holding a grudge doesn't doesn't do anything to the
Person that you hold a grudge against it only does things to ourselves
And we miss this bitterer makes us like you know not trust other people and so, you know
We'd like go of that. Maybe we can forgive ourselves and other people. So what's wrong Katrina says something so fake. Okay, so
Uh, but he right here is the you dumb queer where bright is right. I hate stigmas
Right is right. What is what is what do you mean Katrina?
So fucking fake like what do you mean like?
What is right is right? You know you sound like a
You know
Some kind of supremacist or something it's open panel, but psyche runs the channel
So he's allowed to like have people come and go as he pleases
It's okay. He doesn't want to hear what somebody has to say also because ultimately he is the boss. This is his playground
Right. It's not like I mean it's like
It's like people are here because it's like I what is the title that it's a while anything's anything goes anything does go
But it doesn't mean it's so anything goes including my decision to like kick people off if I want to it's anything goes
You don't know it. It's like, uh
You know, you don't know what you're gonna get but say you're just I mean you're I'm having conversations with spunky
You're they're rambling about that. What's his name? You know that Nick winter who is just a really really weird guess and
Well, say say and
Sinking BG they hit them. They have the potential to be
I've seen them when they're when they are both sober and they are really articulate and will smoke in and
That's a rare thing for the zoomers. That's a
thing for the zoomers
Usually they're all fucking idiots
they're well-spoken and uh yeah I mean they're smart they're smart they're obviously smart guys
they're obviously smart guys and it's like but maybe you know some they're not smart people
they get a little bit like oh i'm very smart you know you can tell they they know they're smart
right they really like you know
They're like, oh, we're so we're so smart. We're so smart, right? Okay. Anyway
It's good. Okay. It's gonna be smart people. It's gonna be smart people, but it's like, you know part of intelligence is like
No, we really don't know very much
Intelligence is knowing what to shut your mouth, you know, right? Uh-huh
Oh the logo we like the logo which one we're nor
Oh, the nor yes, that's the nor on the logo. Yes, it is. Yeah
I mean, it's like I just
No, it's not you're underwater
Yeah
Like sick like sick like I've seen him before on other people's panels and
He's a well-spoken and funny individual
When he's when he's drinking vodka all day evidently, that's obviously new
Okay, love you Trevor. Thank you for coming. You're a great guy. Thank you for coming. Thank you for your
Opinion, I mean, it's like I'll let you back sick sick. Just listen sick. You have to stop being so
Argumentative with me. I know you're argumentative
Just don't argue with me
Argue with it. Yeah, the cat on Kenny Valley sort of looking sort of almost
Parents almost Korean but half Korean. You know what I mean? Who's he talking to? He's talking to somebody talking to you psyche
Oh, yeah. Oh, okay. Hey sick. Guess what? I
Well, thank you it didn't go well actually it didn't go bad because it said like it there were over a hundred people that
In the traffic, you know, it had over a hundred hits. That's pretty good
But there's only but nobody commented on it in the chat. I also I can't bring the rumble chat on my stream yard
It doesn't it doesn't go through that so it kind of be hard to use and plus you have to set up a new stream through
It's kind of a hassle to do you can use that rumble has it's called rumble studio
And again, here's the thing, I keep psyche, you understand, I'm sure, that I can say
that I don't like you, and I say that in the efforts of transparency, but I can also still
advise you and give you my own knowledge that can be beneficial to you.
a thing where you would rather ignore it.
And that's fine, that's what you want to do.
Because if you don't like me, then why would you offer me good advice?
Why wouldn't you offer me advice to misleading me?
What's wrong with that?
Because maybe a psyche, maybe because I have,
maybe because the way that you see the world is different from the way that I see the world
and just because I don't like you doesn't mean I have to wish negative on you.
Maybe the way that I maybe the way that I see the world is just because I don't like you doesn't mean
I have to hope that you're for your downfall
Yeah, maybe maybe that's the way things are. Here's the thing psyche. You have not yet given me a reason to
Really dis I mean you kicked me out and all that right for whatever
You haven't given me a reason to really dislike you. Okay, so
know about rumble I've been here I can give you I can give you advising okay
Okay, I mean I just did it for like you know shits and giggles and you know just to have a this is a can I can
Know I can stream to it. So I tried it. It was right and Apple was started for shits and giggles as well
Yeah, you know that
Computer club shits and giggles. Oh, it was just a computer club. Just maybe rumble will get big
Maybe rumble will get big who knows I could I could but I think it's never gonna be here's the thing
Let's not kid ourselves rumble is never going to be as big as YouTube, but
The point is you need to have alternatives diversity in your platforms, right?
I hear you. I hear you. I know about rumble. I've been here. I can give you advice
Okay, you have not yet given me a reason to dislike you. Okay. Well, you know, okay, it's like I don't
You have not yet given me a reason to dislike you.
I got you. I got you. I got you.
No, I'm saying thank you. I appreciate you.
You don't have to appreciate me.
You already don't appreciate me in all honesty.
I do.
I just like being a helping hand.
It makes me feel better knowing that I'm giving a gay man
an LGBTQ disabled man.
Hell, it makes me feel happier.
And I want to see you're a good guy because you helped a gay person.
And I want to see I don't want to be I'm a bad person.
No bell prize. I'm not a good guy. I'm a bad person
I'm trying to make up for my sins by helping this disabled cable black
Well, I don't know if it'll make up for all your sins just helping me
I think I'm you know, but you know, I want to make up for all the bad with all the disabled black man
And I'm helping okay. Okay. Okay. Oh boy. How are you random guy? Hey. Hey a whole random guy
What kind of call you know, I came here for the the intervention. I thought we were doing. Oh, yeah
Yeah, we see we fooled you. We got you here. So we want to talk to you. So, you know, you see give a problem
We're gonna take you to a random treatment facility
We're gonna offer you 30 days
Yeah, how about I give you 30 how about I give you 30 snacks to the mouth?
He's not ready guys. He's not ready yet. He's not done. Yeah. No. No. Okay. Well, if you don't go you're going to
You know, then you have die
That's why for you fucking rotten liver that's quite for you
Let's hope it gets well. Okay. Oh, there's a walking talking Stephen Hawking. Oh, that's it. Oh, that's the exorcist
Who was that person yesterday? They were somebody else in the chat. I forgot. Okay. Nobody got a plane ticket. Yeah
We have a plane ticket for you sick sick. It's a nice place. It's a really nice place. I'm you know, Rancho pals Verdes
It's they have yoga. They have yoga. It's it'll be okay. Um, they have they have coffee enemas every day
You can have a coffee enema
You know that will just replace water aerobics some yoga
coffee
Coffee said say do you like coffee? You're spunky. Do you is it do you have a can I ask you spunky?
question
You have like a husband. Oh, I have a boyfriend
Okay, you're boyfriend not like you don't care how long how long have you had a
That boyfriend a year and a half. Oh
Why are there's there's people that are trying to tell me that you have like a husband
No, I don't have a husband. Everybody thinks we're married. We're together a lot and
But like we don't even live together. Are you looking for somebody different on here?
No, he's the one that introduced me to you guys. Well. Oh, that's a red flag
That's not it.
Well, Justin did it.
Yeah, he did.
Justin is such a skeptic.
He doesn't believe in afterlife at all.
Wait, hold on.
Hold on.
He smashed and then he showed you this YouTube channel?
Um, you showed me the YouTube channel like maybe six months before you smashed it. No.
Was it what can I ask more? Sorry, more specifically, you can.
He was on the phone with Gotti and I was like, who the fuck is this guy that keeps calling you?
And like, where was it? The question was, was it before or after he smashed?
Dude, we smashed the first night. So it was okay. So it was after. Okay.
All right. Well, I was going to say that's crazy.
If I was if I was a if I was a woman and I'm and I would literally and and and the guy pulled up psyche I
Would go to police station ask for a great kid
And no honesty
That's why
Yeah, he just like showed me when he was in the chat and I was like I'm gonna go on there and
Then I started coming in here and doing my own thing and it's been fun
Yeah, I
Agree, it is super super cool to be able to
Do this online world? I really do I really do
Like this socially better than some of the real-life social social stuff
Especially after what I've been through but a spunkies Justin Boyle side check. No, I don't believe that
Okay
Mr. Hey, why is he calling me miss fuck you easy hop on?
Why isn't your camera on who mine?
Yes, or see oh you want you want to see me. I want to see spunky. I want to see you
I want to see you. No, well, here's the thing spunk setter camera on many times
So I'm not gonna ask her and do it. Yeah, you're a camera
Thanks, big mine was on earlier, but then you don't have to thank me
I
Feel like you are just saying this guy is like let's see. Well, what do you have to say buddy? Let's hear
No, I feel like you're here. I'm sorry. Let's hear. Did you hear back hold back from spunky there? I
Feel like you know back. Yeah, you held back. Well, I think you wanted like what do you have to say?
Nothing feels like you have your own ideas. No somebody
I'm at the gas station and these uh, I was talking to somebody they said something so I do I had to go on mute
I was I was uh, I was taking the streams in New Jersey. Huh?
You live in New Jersey?
No, why?
Well, you were like at the gas station and the guy the tendons talking to you
No, no, no somebody in the car next to me
New Jersey is one of the only states that they don't do self-serve. You have an attendant has to I don't have
I would hate that
That's a law
Would you hate I think in New Hampshire pumping my gas? I just I want to be like in control man core
I don't like valet either for some reason
Yeah, there's um, there's one gas station around here that actually does that and I look at him. I'm like
Like no, I'm doing it myself. I also feel like while I'm capable like I want to just you know
Maybe when I'm an old person and I can't I'll appreciate it, but right
Yeah, it feels weird. Yeah
Well
Hey guys, I by the way, I did start my merchandise store. See there's my new logo
He's in the new logo and so it's it is on some merch you can go to the
Inside this my my my channel. It says shopping or else, you know
Just like you wake ins on a teespring. Okay, there you go. That's really it's really cool sticker. Huh? It's really cool
Yeah, I really like it
Yeah, I'd be able to look good on this on the sweatshirts and stuff
They got I got like some sweatshirts and the stickers right now who made it like he did you didn't make that
It's a the logo. Yeah, it was you know, I made it with AI on Canva
And yeah, and it just came out really perfect and yeah, I really did
Yeah, so yeah imagine good times pumping your gas bro. I wouldn't I wouldn't
Bro, if I roll up to gas station and he was pulling my gas, I would pull out a projectile weapon.
That's what I'm saying.
Not a weapon.
My hand would be reaching into my center console.
It would be like a blaster.
It would be a dart blaster.
I would pull out a dart blaster.
I would pull out a dart blaster on good times.
I'll pull out a dart blaster.
You really don't need to yet.
You're in a car, so you can just, you know, pretty much get paid.
No, I would not use my car against a human being.
That's awful.
Never.
I know that.
I was being serious.
I would never do that.
OK, I know you wouldn't say that.
I would much rather use a bulldozer.
Oh my god.
Well, let's not or like something. That's like gonna like crush all the ligaments and bones and everything
Take that picture. This is chachi PT made this it like depends on the soil
Here's the thing like you can crush a body, but it's like the soil is like
Well, the soil is soft and they're just gonna go into the soil and you're not actually gonna crush them
Right. Okay. Say say say say let's not talk about you're rambling against me. I'm sorry. I don't want to hear that
Yeah, I don't want to hear it. I'm just saying that's how you that's how you do these things
Running people over with a fucking
I'm not talking about people. I'm just saying like organic objects. Nope. No people. No
No violence against white white white even bring it no violence against people. I do not believe in violence against people
love people and I hope I could see you look like for the world this is code
for seeing this is code no this is not code you're saying this you're saying
this you're saying this I'm not saying that you're saying I'm telling you that
I do not you got retort you're being weird no you're being weird you're being
weird say you're being I'm telling you
and then say, oh, I don't have people in the car
You know that nature has, like, everything is full of, like, organic matter, okay?
Right, right
We're talking about organic matter and not souls
Human beings are too
I'm talking about souls
I'm talking about people
We're both, we're both organic
We are organic matter and we're so
I'm not talking about souls and human beings, okay?
It's not being weird
Come on, dude
Start hitting on sports again
the TOS of all platforms and I'm against violence.
I'm a very, I believe in nonviolence.
OK. Yeah, the simple.
So the only the only things that I will be bulldozing are not alive
and organic.
OK, well, let's hope so. OK, anyway, you're compostable.
Thank you.
Hey, human bodies are compostable.
That's a point I have to make.
So you're saying you're psychic.
You're saying all these things.
And so when you get a strike.
For saying that is it my fault or is it your fault? I'm not gonna get a strike because I'm telling you
I'm telling you directly that I am not saying that and I'm trying to avoid saying that
Specifically so when you get a strike for saying this is it gonna be my fault?
I don't get a strike for saying all right then paper okay the paper that okay, then I'm gonna I'm gonna take that as a
No, I'm gonna understand. I don't know the decomposition of the body as a no. Thank you very much
He seems dangerous like yeah, I don't trust yeah, I know I was gonna say is that something about something about
So okay, so I won't say the name but somebody was buying up a lot of farmland in America, right and a lot of land, right?
And then they're also studying how to decompose human bodies to feed like the be fertilized or basically in there
Look, okay, and they turn your body and it's like organic matter. Yeah, you can you can like help, you know
How's the earth? Yeah, and this guy wants me to camp up. Are you fucking kidding me? Yeah
Like no, thank you. All right. Thank you. I want your opinion. I got I got new glasses today
Okay, I don't normally wear them on the stream. I don't usually wear them outside of work. So I have to oh
I like them
I love them. You're getting glasses. I I mean, I
I kind of like my glasses too. Yeah 40 looks good on you. It's good
Oh, that's sweet. Thanks.
You look, I see, and you look, you're still just cute.
You're not like, you didn't turn into a nerd, you know?
It's like...
Well, I tried to get ones that, like, some of them
really made me look like a nerd, I thought.
And then I wanted ones that, like, weren't so,
so, so nerdy, but...
Yeah.
Well, they look really good. They look I like the the frames. They're
Yeah, they're rose gold. Oh, they're gold. Yeah. Oh, nice. I was looking at like a look like some nicer pairs and glasses
Like there's they're not too much nicer than these. These are for you. These are
Those suit you well. That's the kind like exactly what my son got ones like yours
They have this blue they've blocked out the blue the blue like the blue light. Yep
and stuff which is like bad for you for a long term. I mean I don't know but that's true but you
know supposedly this blue light is kind of negative. Yes people with nothing to lose like
family or job ask people to come up their discord doxers. Billy bats here's the thing I'm not I'm
not a that's not necessarily what I'm advocating for but what I am saying is
If if if you're going to be doing things that are so negative, let's say, right?
not
Including doxing, right? I want to say promise
Predominantly doxing right if you're gonna be doing doxing if you're gonna be doing negative things, but you're too scared to show your own face
I think that makes you a coward
Think that makes you a bitch. That's I'm just I'm just a psyche. I'm sorry. I'm just psyche
I'm just I'm just responding to the comment. Yeah, I know I agree with you. I'm saying them and so
So so yeah, if you if you want to I
Yeah, I don't agree with doxing at all. I want to make that clear
But but if you're if you're gonna do that if you're gonna do something like that at least have the balls to show your face your own face
Yeah, at least you know that just goes to show that that you're of
Showing that you're afraid to inflict on
Others inflict what you're doing on others. It just makes you look weak
Right, right, okay. I agree with that and yeah
If you docks you should be prepared to be docks because it's and it's like you you should be docks if you're docks because you know
The first thing I heard about doxing was like this community
The stupid TV show 90 day fiance. There's all these content creators and they
Uncover all these secret Facebook rooms with their competitors
Where they're like giving away their kids preschools and stuff like that. It just gets it was like just it's nasty
Like it's got so mean and like awful of the
Docs if you think all the pictures of all the family and and so it's just like it goes really really far for like no reason
It's like some of these it's like it's just the I mean, that's just a stupid show. I mean, this this is even worse
I was lighting up and have so fun
Got he's back. Hey, Gotti
so
So sick
So, yeah, no harm, no foul, Sig, but, you know, let's have a nice conversation, we don't have to be so dramatic.
Now, Sig, what's with you and Flirty Diamond, what's going on?
I've been communicating with Flirty Diamond, she's not been talking to me lately.
I'm very worried.
Why is there any association to be made?
That's not your twin sister?
No, never mind never mind. Anyway, okay, so yeah, he's a nice nice small guy who loves math. Yeah, I love math, too
Mathematics right see again diamond. Hell nah, but you didn't give something going on with her for a little bit or something
You know, so so it went from my it went from my sister to somebody that I'm oh, yeah
I remember you were on a show you took a you took a dump on her live and then you showed your butthole, right?
And it was right presumes that this is true
Okay, well is that is that what you're saying right? It's the statement
You you made you said something followed by right. So you presume it's presumably what you're saying is true
right
It was I know it's true. I know it's true. I don't I don't
on the clip I
Don't recall that occurring. I mean if you want to share it with me. Obviously, you don't have to play it
I understand that you can't play it on your stream, but if you would like to send me the stream
I would be more than willing to play it on my rumble stream. It'd be really funny
psyche
So if I did do that, I would like the clip. It would be funny to play it. I mean you said you've seen it before if you could
If you if you could share
Okay, oh, thank you. Please share that sounds funny. So I'll ask I like it. Did you see did you see the clip of Aldi?
He was spinning on his chair, but make it
Like you did you see that clip it was literally yesterday
Okay
Well, I'll do you better than that.
He's gonna leave. Bye, bye, bye. Thank you.
No, don't make him leave.
No, he didn't make any left. He left on his own. I didn't do anything.
Oh, what are you doing? How are you doing, man?
Good. How are you doing, man? Here's Doddy.
I'm doing okay. He made him leave.
I did it. He left on his own.
Cool guy.
Wow. Cool guy.
What's up. Goddy's in the house.
You got it. You got to growl whenever you say God.
Yeah. Whoa. Hey.
Hey guys, look at my. Yeah, I mean you try.
My new tripod
Yeah, you're other than was like loose or something right yeah, but it then this one doesn't fit my
Tablet in it, so I can't really use it, but I fixed the other one kind of it's working
But this is for my cell phone now, and I'll have it at the pier now
I can go like that and have it in the air fish tacos had the light on it too. Oh
It's a light on yeah
What you get like a fog machine, too? Yeah, like in like a
Strip plate back there. Yeah, and a pole get a pole stripper pole
Okay, now do a little dance
That's his anal probe.
Watch this one, it goes like that, it goes like this, it goes like that, it goes like
that.
Oh my god.
Oh no.
It's the colon spreader 3000.
Oh my god.
I love that it works.
Dude, Smunky loves it.
What the hell?
No.
It's like an online colonoscopy.
I can give you one now, and I have my own.
Okay, oh, you don't okay. No, I'll be I'll be there. Okay. Anyway, remote probe. Oh, yeah
She does go to just sell a tear charity. You call me a f-a-g-g-o-t
Katerina. Hey Katerina. I don't remember you. You're you're a mod for somebody. Who are you mod for vegan patreon or something?
And then you said terrible slanderous things about me and other people in her chat. I saw I saw women are really mad
down there. I don't know why. She must be. She must be. She has stupid, stupid humans.
A disgruntled, disgruntled bitch.
Okay, see I was right. I was right. I was right if he is well, you know any women
Mr.. Big Pipe's is big is being patriots top. Oh God. What do you know that Kevin?
You're not with his harmonica, please Jesus
Right stupid stupid human stupid human will equate
Stupid human will equate spunky laughing at me as oh, they would be a cute couple
But then when she laughs and giggles with another dude, it's not weird or anything
Just giggling like a friend
If you were with if you were with her, I would be like girl girl. I mean we need to get that's hilarious
Sponkeys got an awful face God bless the soul. Is this the Aldi want to be?
No, no, no
He came he came from the Audi. Yeah, I think he's trying to be an Aldi
Yeah, he's from Aldiverse see from what the one caber so whatever it's called
The Aldi 1k.
He's the Aldi 1k versus person.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, me and Q were, you know, mods for him and fucking...
There came this little guy, and we love him.
We love him?
Fuck you.
The angry person said you got an ugly face.
Oh, that's okay.
I think I am uniquely handsome.
Yeah, but I don't think Spongebob is uniquely beautiful in any way. She's a cute God bless her heart
That's why that's why women have vaginas and there's other ways to generate intimacy and affection
Wow, oh, he's pulling he's pulling that jet. No, look she's cute what I smash
if it depended on if it depended on a lot of people yes it depended on the
entire planet to restart the world I would
You'll never have a choice to smash yeah, I would not especially not from you
I think I'm a uniquely handsome man. I think I'm ugly
But also I'm good looking and so it's it's I have a face
I have a face that you look at for a while
I have a face that you you don't look at it immediately. You look at it for a while
Then there's faces that you look at immediately and it's just ugly
But then there's also souls
There's also the personality of the person and when you when you determine people's personalities and
And their souls that there's more of a cumulative sort of do you guys like pickles at all combination? No
Have you had Kool-Aid pickles you can make
And he can fucking produce pickles. It's
Okay
Right, I'm aware you dude. You don't have to tell me that you think I was born yesterday
I know that Gotti and Ziggy are discord buddies. I'm not stupid
What do you mean?
I
We bang we bang a woman in front of me. Yeah
Oh, that's weird.
I can't even know.
You didn't have to do that.
No, I'm not
No, I was talking about you. I was talking about you if you yeah
If you could be my woman, can he bang you?
Like in the same room, I mean, you know
It turned in it turned into
Come on, turn into Spunker. Spunker Smite!
Yeah, these guys are creepy I'm gonna leave to these guys are like these guys are kind of like G
you know what I mean you know G you I don't I want to I don't think I want to stay here
What's what you don't know what wait hold on can you say that again? I don't know what's where it's grapey or rude because
How is that what do you mean? What's worse? Are you fucking kidding me?
What's worse, but you're like is it worse to be rude or grapey? I think it's worse to be grapey
Yeah, I think it's worse to be grapey. What the fuck?
I think it's definitely worse to be grapey than rude
What is crazy that's crazy it's like take off the G take a take off the G off the word and there is yeah
Yes, there's your idea
To say to say being grapey
Is less bad than being rude is insane
Because what do you mean what what is page gonna do what is page gonna do for you about
Being grapey is less bad than being rude
Yes, because they're making a bad joke, but you're dead-ass serious. So like
Wouldn't you be concerned about somebody being
Grapey that word you understand the connotation of that word
You don't think you would you don't think your your logic your sense your sense of self-preservation
Would not lead you to be more concerned about talking about somebody that's being grapey
We're on me rude. I'm sorry. So you're concerned about your little ego being
Concerned and being grapey. Hey, that's odd. I find that odd
This sounds odd it's not ammonia it's methanol
It's methanol. That's what you're thinking of. Yeah
Levels are so high that I know what it is. Yes, it's methanol
meth meth
If you do a meth thing. No some methamphetamine is methanol
Not the same thing. It's backstage
Okay, hold on a second. Damn, man. I
I love that kid. You know how you know how young he is guys
He's like to want
Like 18 years old I'm like literally a fetus. I just came out of the womb
You're too young to be here then if you're if you're only
Hey, you're right.
See, what a buzz kill.
Oh, jeez.
Jesus.
I know.
I'm like, oh, what happened?
He is a smart kid.
He's articulate, but obviously he's drug off his ass right now, but.
Oh, he's going fucking vodka and fucking pills and everything.
Both him and BG are.
SIG and BG, in a community full of Zoomers who don't have a mind for themselves, who are not articulate in the slightest,
I would say SIG and BG are the most articulate, but they get so into this mindset of complete fucking horseshit.
Who is this?
It's Trevor.
I'm sorry. Yeah
We just pulled ever you pull everybody up and you number introduces
I'm sorry
I'll be right back. Okay, sweetie. Okay, sweetie. I'll be careful. He's a friend of the show. Oh, okay, cool
He's a fella. He's a fellow gay like me.
I don't agree with what you said about BG, but well, thank you random guy. Thank you random for the super chat
Something about Benny, and I'm like, oh, Benny's John, he just talks fucking horseshit.
And Corndog was like, oh, well, he's still a racist, is that any other?
And Corndog probably had a point, but what if you tried to be human to these people?
And you know what I mean? Have a conversation with them.
That's a good point.
Maybe they wouldn't, you know, especially these 20-year, these kids in their 20s who,
some day they had this mindset and they don't know a fucking thing.
Nobody, nobody is who they were in their 20s once they...
Well, and not just that, but I bet they would cry if they got a tattoo in their ditch, bitch.
Well, I don't know what it is, but I'm sure it's, I don't know what that is, like right in the, on the opposite side, right in the opposite side of your fucking elbow, like right in the, in the, in the, inside of your elbow, okay, I got you.
Yeah, like on the inside, oh yeah.
Okay, hi.
Yeah, well, yeah, you're gonna be you know, you never even fucking said it like that to me
When I came up you didn't say hi. Hi, Ziggy. Oh, thanks
Hi, Ziggy
When I go out on a date, you're gonna go on a date with me Ziggy. What the hell? No, we gave her a little bit
No, no, are you sure? Are you sure? What are we doing? Please? What are you doing a date? Are you gonna go on a date with me, Ziggy?
I'm very attracted
I love your name reminds me of that little comic book character that bald guy with
That's where I got it from. Oh
Yeah, okay
Yeah, are you talking about the
Ziggy yeah, the paper the paper. Yeah. Yeah comics. Yeah, I would go I would go to school and fucking my fucking
grandparents would fucking load me up with fucking on the Sunday paper and fucking
Yeah
Next thing I know my name is Ziggy
Gotta love gotta love grandpa. My grandmother used to like she buy these takeout
like eight hours of Popeye like the original Popeye like you know she's like oh kids love
we're kids we're like what the fuck is this oh i don't know maybe Popeye is good i don't know i think
i think we're a little bit we're a little bit oh we were a little bit
but okay okay okay uh let's go see he's right here back today do you want to come back in
he's here just look at him guys hold on look oh he gets fucked up dude
he gets fucked up i haven't known him for fucking five years now he can't hear us
Look at him.
We do.
It was all wet, just a little bit.
Was that safe?
Safe.
Very good.
That is real. Yeah. She's just burping his Colostomy bag. We got like four PSPs in this room. This is all it takes.
Okay. Oh, so so JT. I have to I would I have to play the song which are JT because it has rain and JT
And I don't think they heard it yet. I think what is it called called the troll slimes?
Yeah, Billy bats Billy bats you can say a lot of things
Billy bats
You say a lot of things you can say a lot of things, but you're not gonna say I have work I
Don't have worse face are than ETC. That's a
I don't wanna sing. He's playing a song. Hold on.
with the tarot pack
turn out a pocket out of touch
your trauma done
I don't know
keep that frown cause trolls
make the world go round
no no you have it
listen listen listen
stop it stop
listen there
there's a part where we got rain now
j.t. and reigns
devilishly hot
if lucifer had a twitch they'd co-host
But even they know not to cross these vibes, then there's Alice yelling you're all the same dudes got more clones
I'm mute I boot I laugh so hard while I shuffle my deck and pull your card
But guess what psyche don't fold you're just another name in the block troll
That was over. That was over.
One more time. One more time.
Hey!
Shut up!
Hey, don't just date me. Shut up.
I'll say whatever I want.
Okay
Yes, what was that can we make sure that we say one thing ever like we never say shut up to each other
Okay. Oh come on. It was in a playful way. It wasn't even like a...
Right. Yeah.
Because I was like, you're talking over my song.
I know, I know, I know. All right. Well, if you want to play it again.
No, no, no. That was it. I played it. So that's why I just wanted to play it once.
What do you think, Cardi? Did you like it?
I thought it was pretty good.
Yeah, yeah.
Um
God he likes the other side of this it goes got in a wheelchair and then it goes and then it goes
No, no, I already copyrighted you for that one. Oh my god. Oh my god. You did not you cannot I am I copyrighted the song
It's you all you copyrighted it
Well, he's a member it is copyrighted to me
I get rights to share it without even attributing it so you know it's not well then it's not how much money did you make up that song?
There's nothing yet, but I'm I'm able to
Have a whole album soon. I'm gonna have a whole album. Oh, yes, I will I'm gonna be bigger than Michael Jackson
bigger than Michael Jackson
Wait, no, it's not slander. Where'd you get this crap about the wheelchair anyway?
From you from you and what are you watching you?
It's okay. I don't I don't know you say you have no legs. I think you have your word, okay?
I don't know what the fuck's going on with you. I don't know
No fucking drugs
Cat goblin
We just
Hold on. Watch this. Watch this. I can tell a fake laugh a mile away.
How about this one? Hey, listen to this one.
I don't really want to laugh at you if you're in a wheelchair.
Do it again.
All right.
That's Jim Nick.
I think it's maybe Crystal. I'm not sure.
He's got that little girl voice.
She sounds like she's 15 for real.
Maybe younger, like 12.
You should get a sound board.
Well, this is my sound board.
All right.
I can make one.
I just have a limited amount of sound.
All right.
Oh, my God.
Stop.
All right.
This driver.
Yes, sir.
Yes, he did.
Aw, man.
Yeah, you guys got to try to look at that sad face.
That's damn cute. I'll be damned.
I'm the happy one.
Aw.
That is hilarious.
I just pretty noticed that. That is great.
Very nice.
Yours is so depressing.
I just found it off of Google. I found it off of Google and that's what I went with.
It's like some some little kid in the back of the car while it's raining you can get
a toy at the toy store. So you just go, oh, that's me, sir. Absolutely. Oh, somebody's
Okay
Yeah, we have two drivers two psyches
Next we miss you. I miss a lot like what's going on nothing. What's going on with you? Oh
I'm not I'm taking care of little chicks. Oh
Chickadees
Yeah, what are they talking about was crazy
What's crazy it sounds like they're getting mad
No, we're getting where they get mad about everybody's had a we're having fun. Everyone's had a fun
He's getting offended nobody only person getting offended is psyche
I'm gonna talk to Shaggy, is that allowed?
Yes, Shaggy!
That guy, Shaggy gets offended, and it's a temper tantrum.
See? Like I said...
He starts kicking around, and he's like,
I'm gonna kick here, and I'm gonna kick here, and I'm gonna kick here.
Why are you getting mad?
I would feel sorry for him, if he wasn't such a little shit.
Sorry, what was your question, guy?
Yeah.
was your question sir was your question yes go ahead here one away here talk to him
I thought you said everybody was nice yeah oh I'm a nice guy I'm a really nice guy
what do you mean no I'm not sure I'm a really nice guy you are a articulate I'm
a nice guy what do you mean low key no I'm a nice guy like yeah I thought you
Everybody is nice. I thought you were just not saying anything. You should continue doing that
Okay, what's your question you said that you had a question? What's your question, sir?
Ziggy shut the fuck up
you shut the fuck up you shut the fuck up close your close your fucking retarded close your
develop and retarded piehole okay ziggie you're you're a fully grown and developed man and you're
fucking retarded shut your fucking piehole shut the fuck up and let the guy ask questions
shut the fuck up you are my child oh
Would literally I would it would be a problem if that was the case if that was the case
It would be a problem for you my god
Are you kidding if it was the question shut the fuck up ziggie the fuck down
Ziggy I would literally it would be a problem. It would be a problem. It's on the safety. That's quiet for you
Okay. Oh, yeah. What was the question? Please ask
Everybody's retarded and full of idiots. That's your number one. You're ready. You're already starting on a false premise
Everybody's retarded. Look at psyche. Psyche is like a millennial. He's like Gen X. He's fucking an imbecile
Okay, so it has nothing to do with age, your generation has nothing to do with intelligence
or your ability to discern the world around you.
Age and the generation has nothing to do with your ability to discern the world around
you.
Nothing.
Would do that I would beat you know you would not know you would not I promise that that would never happen
Your friends and promise you that that would never happen. I promise you that I would do that
Yes, I would
I know what I'm saying, it doesn't matter if I'm a vodka or not.
I know what the fuck I'm talking about, if I'm opening my mouth and I'm speaking, it's
because I know what the fuck I'm saying.
A lot of people just like to talk.
A lot of people just like to talk and just say things. If I'm saying something, there's a reason that I'm saying it.
At the least, there's a reason that I'm saying it. It doesn't matter. I'm drunk right now.
What are you saying? It don't matter. It do not matter.
It do not matter.
Hold on. Hold on. That's the problem with him.
Sig you get the problem with you is that you're fucking stupid. It doesn't matter bro
You're stupid all the time. It doesn't matter. It doesn't matter if you're drunk. You're still stupid
It don't matter and do not matter. You're stupid still stupid
It doesn't matter, but let me talk to Ziggy while he's sober and you sound like just fucking retarded
Shut the fuck up. Yeah, I know
So it don't matter, it don't matter, shut up.
You wouldn't fucking get along with someone that fucking...
You're fucking an idiot, bro. Shut the fuck up.
I'm an idiot, yeah.
I think that SIG and BG are two of the most articulate in a generation from the beginning.
Wow.
Now you're just making yourself...
Now you just ruined the credibility for everything that you just said.
You understand that now I don't want to hear anything that you have to say.
Now I don't want to hear anything that you have to say.
Now you have completely demolished any credibility that you could have had.
No, I know no that guy's a fucking faggot dude, and if you're gonna if you're gonna
Don't say it don't say that word
No, no, no, he was talking about himself
My god
And, you know, Zoomer, not every Zoomer, not everyone on that generation, but a lot of
the Zoomers on the internet, they're just mindless, they don't have a thought for themselves.
But I was just saying that this kid SIG and BG, when they're not being stupid fucking
assholes, like, they are really smart and articulate.
But the problem is they get drunk and they're stupid fucking assholes like all the time BG BG is definitely smart
Yeah
There's a problem. There's a problem. Is there a problem because I'll bite you site. No, no Trevor Trevor
Well, I think I think I'm turning
And I want I want to say something in
And whenever he was talking about what he was talking about, like,
SIG, SIG, literally, I could, dude, I went and trained with SF.
And fucking, I would beat you, I would beat you the fuck up.
Did you do that gay voice you did?
I would beat you to fuck up
Think do that voice you did the gay voice you'd have the other day on psyches do that voice again
If you think it's like that you better watch your fucking mouth
Yeah
I don't I don't like that. That's kind of like reminds me of like black, you know, the people that you would make, you know
Black voices and stuff. It's stereotypical. Is there a black voice? It's like black bass, but with the voice. Yes, there is
Yeah, no, you need to be as stupid as possible. Yes
Yeah, so my point my point was that his regular voice and that voice that he does they're not too far apart
Okay
And what you do
Your concern, okay? Okay, Ziggy. Bye. Oh shit
I'm I'm so drunk I can't even keep up with us. Oh my god, it's already 10 p.m. Oh shit. Okay. That's okay
Oh, no, what happened to 10? Oh, no, no tobacco no tobacco
It's okay. More tobacco tonight
Are you gay Trevor
I
Did it's JT the wolf man. Well, let me just drop my mic. Yeah, I don't know who the fuck fuck my mic. Yeah
Yes, I
Am indeed a homosexual
How are you sir? Are you a heterosexual? I
Am you got it?
You got it. I that's still that's still for upper debate. I'm Trevor
No, it's like you're always trying to convert everybody
You're a wolf man, you don't go around fucking wolves,
they're dogs.
No, I don't do that.
You only need a wolf man.
Yes, and why do you have that dog porn on your computer
for putting on the-
Dude, that was Tiffany playing with her dog Shadow.
She was wearing-
That was not, he was had the dog humping on her back.
No, they were both hot dogs.
Look man, I know what it looks like,
and yes, it basically is what it looks like.
They were both hot, these frogs.
She was wearing new colored spandex. She wasn't okay. I mean it was like this
It's a tiny little picture like it's not that small
It's like why do you bring that up all the time if you don't want to talk about it?
I didn't want to talk about it because I was wondering why you put that there. It's disgusting if it's real
I don't think it's real. It was I saw the dog. The dog had a horrible look on his face
It wasn't real but she definitely that was her dog shadow
You know what JT we'll be showing the picture again. This is it. No, no, no
No, no bc ality
I really do like it almost makes me want to cry like
It really is endearing, like, I just, like, that is your story.
Oh, I'm mad, this shit, I heard, buddy, Gary.
This is me.
That'd be funny.
Trevor, you feel a lot of emotion, don't you?
I'm drunk.
You wrote the deal.
Why?
Why would you?
Why would we?
It's a happy cry.
I hate shadow.
I got a bad dog. This is a bad
Thing to think about but like I wonder how many times Tiffany put peanut butter on her
Nobody did that nobody
It did not do that
On her neck on her neck. Um, yeah, so rain has a sore throat or she would come up here, too
Did she have two black eyes
No, I guess that's how did you know fuck yeah, she does
He knows how the fucking he knows how the hey, that's my woman got it on the guy you
Got it my woman's gonna know her place soon. She'll have to black out soon. Okay
Yeah, fuck yeah, I'm gonna beat the fuck out of her and then make her your woman again
Can you do it? That means you're my woman. Yeah, you do it. Can you do it live? Yeah? Oh, yeah
Well, no, not that and you just but it was he comes on live and
Again, and should be like looking like a raccoon. Yeah, how horrible that be like we're talking to the yellow sun
I'd kick him off the panel
That's fine
What the fuck? That makes like, what, three games on set?
Like, three games on set or no?
Can I ask Gotti a question?
What up, man?
Can I ask you a question, please?
Go ahead.
Gotti, if it were, I'm 37 just today, but if it were 17 years ago,
and I were a cute little twink like I was,
I got a stone cold twink.
I got a nice spot on me. Jesus Christ.
Are you even fighting like this?
Are you into Twinks?
What did he say?
What did I say?
He had to be his dad.
He got it.
And which are you into tweets? Yeah, where's that girl talking?
Is that the fucking page? It's spunky.
God, he's not gay.
How much money does he have?
I'm not gay.
How much money we talking?
I. Oh.
I am God, Trevor. I am God.
You know that. I am God.
Everybody's dead. Listen, Trevor.
I want to kick you out. Oh my god.
I would have spanky, man.
You look good.
I'm gonna kick you out.
Is that okay for me to say that?
Who said that? Oh, no, you look great. Oh, yeah
God's gift, right? Fuckin sick looks like a platypus. I know I wouldn't even give sick the time of day on the street
And it's so funny. Would you give me a time of day? I don't know what you look like, Ziggy
You know like hey, which is the truth I'm like, hey, he's a very articulate funny kid
You know when he's not drunk off his ass and then all of a sudden it's like well fuck you this that and the other it's like
real I'm just
All I've ever done for that kid is try to
Try to put him over. You know what I mean like put him over your knee
You want to fuck that little ugly kid with the hat
When he's not drunk off his ass he's actually in our taking away
You know funny funny kid, but it's just like it's just like man
I put him over and he's like well fuck you you faggot and it's like what?
I've never never heard anything articulate come out of his mouth never
Yeah, the drunken indirings always been it's always been either
Bag it or the n-word or something like that
Yeah, he's gonna impart he's gonna impart his drunk wisdom on to all of us
Hey, Goddy guess what?
What she's going car shopping for mongo tomorrow. Are you serious? Yeah
You're out of your mind
Get him a go-kart
He's already got a like an electric bike. He's gonna kill someone. No, he's not of course. He is
He's gonna run them over on purpose no, he's not just it makes it sound awful. He's not
You ran me over. He killed your dog. He punched the walls. He did not kill my
Me he didn't threaten Justin many times
He just intimidated him a little bit
Puss like it's because my son's got like three inches and like
30 pounds on him. So he's like intimidated by him.
I'm just saying he's taller than him and like bigger than him.
Gross. Is he like mean mugging him and shit?
And like kind of like, I think he's too young.
He's too young right now to get Justin got mouthy with me.
And then my son came out in the kitchen and was like,
is everything all right out here?
You're doing like in a fake deep voice. That's what it actually can look like he did and
Oh, let's see. Oh, yeah, you're cute
No, you're like my old paper boy
Made up man, don't worry about it. Is that AI? No, you want to see the worst
Yeah, where's the where's the one with the dreads? Yeah
I'm looking for it. I'm looking for it
Yeah, I think you should wait on the car
No, I think it's I think it's like a crucial point for it so that he he agreed to get a job and
so like his dad and I are going halfs in on the car and then he's going to be able to take himself to work and
Also when his dad like fails to pick him up to see him at his house
He lives like 30 minutes away
So now he can just like go to be at my house all the time. Well two things don't don't get him anything crazy
one
No, we have a five grand limit.
Make him pay the insurance.
I mean, that's exactly it.
Man, I mean, that's perfect.
Where is he?
So he's going to get a job.
He's going to pay for the insurance and his own gas.
And then it works.
Yeah.
And then we're like, he put me down.
That's fair.
Then he can get out of Justin's face.
Yes.
Well, then he'll have something to do.
And maybe he won't be so like pent up and grumpy, you know.
And Justin will move in.
I told Justin to move in around like a tiny grumpy.
Oh, my God.
There really is grumpy. He's we live in like a like a city area so he can like go to his friend's
house and stuff all the time but he just like his friends are all working and they're not off at the
same time and
So he's 16 he's almost 17. He'll be 17 in October. So you think he's responsible enough to have a car? Okay
He um, he really is like a good kid. It's just that him and Justin are having like a who's dick is bigger competition
Here we go. Who's that? That's Cooper. That's my other one
That's not you. Wow
Do you want to see one of my Halloween costumes?
Do you want to see a dress?
One of my Halloween costumes. You already saw it. Oh, the truckie. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, look
Okay, oh, there we go. Yeah
So good
No, you shouldn't have done chucky. You should have done his wife. I know
But that was that was what I had at the time
I love it. It's very very good. It's very good. Very good. It's good. It's good. I like it. I like it. I like it
Let's see. How are we doing in chat? Let's see.
We are doing okay in chat. Chat looks good.
Chat looks kind of beautiful.
Yeah, chat's having a good night.
Yeah, yeah.
Me too.
Gotti.
He thinks he stinks.
I want God to be my dad so bad.
I know, I know me too, me too.
I want to give my godfather, not my dad.
Oh, no, I kind of want God to be my dad.
Goddy, will you be my dad?
No, we're all of our dads.
He's not my fucking dad.
We won wait listen for the right for the right price. I'll be anybody's dad
Sorry, we did leave you my grandma got it. Come on. Wait. Is that the other way around if you are
An hour here can be your dad, okay?
No
$120 an hour
a good sense of humor like Gotti just did and I remember having an argument with Alex McQueen
and I'm like you know we're going at it and I'm like suck my dick Alex he's like don't
offer me a favor friend and I just thought that was so brilliant I never saw Alex say that to you
Alex he loves giving oral sex. He does. Oh, yeah
I know I know
No Alex would love that he really would
Alex the queen right I
Like it I like a girl with a clean voice and she has a clean voice
You're disgusting
Oh, thank you
You change that picture
It ain't that big shit, really.
Guys, what do you think about like a picture like a shirt with Magic Johnson's photo on it and it says stay positive
Is that a magic Johnson man? He has AIDS. What are you talking? No, that's why I said stay positive. Oh my god, get it
No, I don't want to play with that games. No, I swear
They have they have that shirt on on on T-Mu right now
I think that's pretty funny, but I have a really I don't I thought it was funny with South Park, but
Uh, I'm HIV positive. I never had AIDS
Are you positive HIV positive? No, I'm not really not but not full-blown. No, you did that joke wrong man. Okay, like
Okay, I'm sorry. I forgot it exactly. Okay. Are you positive? Are you positive? I got the joke wrong. Are you positive?
Are you HIV positive? Yes, that's what you're supposed to say. That's the joke
This guy's HIV positive
Who you are you sure? Are you sure are you positive?
There's a there's also this let me see there's this
Hey speaking of AIDS, what happened to Minnie Manson?
She never came back
He's been back. See how he's been back since he's we have a little
Enduring he was by he he doesn't want to be
Don't say
Just don't refer to me man. Stop it stop it
It will be angry
I wanted to ask you, you had brought it up.
What was that, uh, speaking of AIDS, speaking of AIDS,
what was that documentary you said about?
Oh shit, is that UJT?
Yeah, but why is it a woman?
Oh yeah, that was a good movie.
That's when the brain is looking at you in the mirror.
Yeah, they made us watch it in like high school.
I keep saying Saint because I'm a drunk fucking asshole.
Sike, beg my pardon.
Yes, yes, sir.
Yep, and I know
You know saying
Do you know st. Ten got a patient zero is patient zero was Tom Karla
Oh, yeah
World mansion he was in a mold mansion documentary
Will mansion have you heard? Yeah, three monkey fever
No monkey fever
By Fauci created that shit. Yeah, I know and it was also just to like blame gay people again for everything wrong
Yeah, he did it again with COVID. I was so sick of that. That's why everybody with the vaccine has AIDS now
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
What's up?
Yeah, but it's like
You can tell us, Summer.
Hi, Summer.
Battle.
Never a battle, too.
Beautiful boobies are always team players.
I'm going to shout out to you.
You're a bag.
Hey, I'm gonna point out like um, I'm in
Why can they be like gay
Can you cut swords with music please
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I think I'll be over here. Yeah. You can just be in the corner. You can just watch in the corner. No, I think I'll be looking at my phone or some shit. You can be the cuckoo. You can be the cuckoo. I'll piss. No, that's cool. I'm good. Yeah. We've got you a special chair, the cuckthrone. That's nice. Cuckthrone, what? What's up, Vicky?
Why is that love mouth what the hell is that?
Fucking loud
In you almost
Hey, I'm gay
Some of you give us a great tour of our tattoos this morning. It was awesome, right? Oh
Almost everything
Yeah
Oh, you don't have any tattoos. No way
She has like 80 tattoos like I have the Italian flag and the cute one one cheek and I have to keep them flag on the other cheek
Those are some cheeky tattoos, right?
No
You got a you got a dog and a mongo's name. Oh my god. I have kiss marks. I have pink kiss
Kiss marks really
Let's see it. She's gonna show she's gonna show right now. No, I'm not I tattooed Boyle's lips
I put lipstick on him and then
You believe me?
Yeah, fuck her.
He's fucking lying.
Boy, would you ever read that.
He would be like, those are my lips.
I feel like my sound isn't coming through.
Now
I'll go for it
Yeah
He wants to part of that, even though he's completely zoned out.
Who's that talking?
Like, his mic is jacked.
He's Trevor.
He's in his Trevor.
He's in the other room.
He's got his mic down the hallway.
Oh, okay.
I'm not laughing, but that's what it sounds like.
You can't even get the other whore.
Hello, hello, okay, so yeah
Yeah, Russell
I'll be like your stepdad that drinks and hits you
That be cool, no
Give you a nice little shiner. I hope to beat the crap out of Mongo, he gets out of hand.
Well, wait, wait, wait, and then you learn from life, if you get ahead.
Alright, and then I tell him,
now I feel bad and tell him that I love him.
I feel like the 1990s was the last decade I bought.
Kids getting spanked
Let's change the topic. Oh my god talking about I don't know
Thank you. What are you doing stop? Please? Please? I'm looking at the I'm trying to moderate the chat and run the show
I'm sorry. Everybody's trying to talk man. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you guys, but I'm saying
If anyone gets it, once it's a spanking, it's gonna be Ziggy.
Well, stop!
Stop.
Come on, Ziggy.
You know what?
Let's talk about the...
Let's talk about the politics and the...
Basically, we're in a relationship.
Let's not.
No.
Goddy.
No, no, no, no.
Don't say that.
No.
We are.
I don't want to talk about that crap.
No, we're talking about the FDM files today.
No, we're not.
We're not talking about any of them.
Stop it.
We're about to get all kicked off.
We're gonna kick everybody off the panel.
Yeah, let's talk about weed.
What are we talking about weed? I don't like weed
I'm gonna lay you down and God he's laugh rain everybody likes you what are you talking about?
No, not you do it let Justin walk in on us though
If you if you're hey, I'm gonna tell you what
Are you listening yes, we're listening no if you don't listen to them, then you ain't getting this ass
So you better listen to who listen to who
Godie and JT
I want I want you to listen. I mean I'm going to intentionally not listen to them now. I mean I'm intentionally not going to listen to them now.
I
Bet he bet he better be not out of control is what I'm saying
I've got some six inch chill. It's not you threaten me the good time. Okay, so I will threaten you
I'll threaten you too, you're about to get kicked off the show forever!
What kind of pills are you on?
I don't know why would you kick me?
You just rub me the wrong way sometimes
I
Do you love me in all the right ways?
I'll rub you the right way. What do you mean? Okay, let's do it
Come on over. Stop kicking
Happy birthday
What is he depressed about 37 years old
He was mourning his twink death and all that shit 36 is like
Who is that talking is that JT JT he's he's like midlife crisis right now. Oh shit
Midlife that's what it is
Yeah
Daddy
My two dad my two dad
Even though that guy just left it's so much and you can't back on please. I'm gonna start hitting on summer
Hey
Won't you two make out you guys make out for like five minutes. Oh, you mean me me and psyche. Yeah, we're always gonna make out
I was ready to go
Rain, I don't think anybody's even going to get one with the set.
What's the summer thing?
What is this?
I joined her channel today.
Everyone joined Hotness Summer.
Oh, you like summer?
Yeah, I love summer.
She was driving around.
Driving around listening to some good music today.
Like summer more than me?
Well, I was actually doing outreach.
I was just a part of me driving in between.
Do you like summer more than me?
Yes, much more.
What?
Yeah, much more.
I'm okay. I'm okay jaw dropped right now. Yeah, you ask you ask
Okay, this is picture of summary and not summer. I don't know I hate her
I don't like her and I don't like what you do with her. That's perfect
I don't really get two fucks if you like me or not. How about that goes well that goes well with mine
There's deadlifts
She doesn't ever lips I see I saw her lips you asked me a question one time and
The only thing I say
No, not you, bitch. I never was talking about you.
Don't you tell it to me.
No one gives a fuck what you're talking about, bitch.
You want to be disrespectful? I'll make sure you don't get another fucking word on this goddamn panel, bitch.
So I don't know who the fuck you think you're talking to, bitch.
I feel like something's going on in this fight.
I don't really give a fuck, bitch.
He has to be.
I don't give a fuck bitch. I don't give a fuck bitch. No one's here. You had nice hair and that was it
Well, so when you just call me a bitch, so I
Didn't give a fuck about you
I'm with my man, you little motherfucker
Yeah, okay, well psyche psyche better fix this shit real quick
Okay, well, you know
Yeah, just come get in the bed sweetie. I think I'll be over the wall. Yeah, he'll fix you. Don't crawl up and bend over again.
Yeah, yeah. Hey, you better get in the bed sweetie.
Yeah, bend over. Bend, he needs you. Go over there and crawl up and put that little white ass up and white up his eye area.
It'll be okay. Arch the bed back real good. He's got you.
It'll be okay in the morning. Arch the bed. It'll go in better.
Yeah, man, you better arch your back for me. Motherfucker, please
Bye-bye
Your wet dream couldn't handle it, so you need to start a whole new fucking night
Night night, bitch. Night night. Night night, bitch. Night night, bitch. Night night, bitch. Night night, bitch
Hey, hey, holler
You don't you don't you don't come out of there trannies. No, I'm gonna come across trannies
Yeah, I'm a tranny. Yeah, I'm a tranny fucking idiot
Guy awakens psyche. God are you waking me up? I like it. God you're waking psyche. Oh, you're making me like my cupid. Oh
This is cute. Oh, it's not me sure. Oh, it's not you. It's somebody else. No, take them out
Okay, guys, there's a fake god. There's a fake god II like
Go find the highest bridge and jump up that bridge.
What is it says
What birdo when you need her?
Hey
Psyche you need to kick this bitch. Well, I'm not going anywhere, bitch. Yeah, you are going somewhere
They're gonna be besties tomorrow these two
Hello guys, hello
I just clipped that sorry every time I jerk off. I'm gonna listen to that. I know what that mouth. Do you know do it again?
Really live in
She doesn't live in our life
No, thank God for that. God damn it. Thank God
You're welcome. Yeah, I'm gonna put that thank you God. They're not putting me in their life
Yep, anytime summer. I
Got that's my ring time. That's awesome. Thank you
That's awesome
You like talking dirty, huh?
No, you're just a bunch of fucking simpsons.
Let's leave this backstage, honey.
No, you're a fucking bitch.
You're a fucking reject loser.
You're a bitch.
You're both reject losers.
You're a raunchy wanker.
I like that.
Psyche, how do you put up with this bitch?
I don't want to do it.
Well then leave mother fucker. I just say I'm not leaving because I'm here to stay
I'm gonna stay. I'm here. I
Just put up with you Ziggy because I like you. Oh
You're talking about somebody else. Zoom bitch. What do you think?
He puts up with you. He likes me. There's a difference. We're not the same. No, no
You heard what he said. Shut up. Yeah
You can you can't even do it in the ball rings
No, I could do it like summer
Do it come on Bill
Every time you do that the Bell moves he can't do it back. She can't do it back
Fuck you
Fuck summer the turkey shoot David
I was thinking of of the you know the panel like we have the
Just to give you the new way to do the the gongy thing. Think about lowering the price.
No, the blue thing. No, that's what we're doing.
Why, you don't get any money?
Wait a second. Sponky doesn't know who Summer is?
What? I know who Summer is.
Oh, I'm sorry. I don't know who any of you guys are.
Oh, I look like Sponky.
Yeah, me and Sponky actually like each other.
She has nice friends.
I like Sponky.
I don't like Summer.
That's it, period.
Good.
I don't give a fuck.
It's like a turkey.
You got to make a turkey sound.
She can't even do it
No, we know why they're up here talking to us and not laying in some pussy right now
Because I hate girl, I'm get more dick than you
That's it, that's how how many inches can you fit in your throat at once?
do you have gag reflexes yeah no I give I give okay you have good head do you
nine nine I'll give you a nine what oh yeah I don't think I want that
Don't
You turn them out you guys like you turn them out you guys are fucking no
Yeah, you jerks Trevor and Ziggy
I'll put the D down in the throat. Yeah for sure
Alright
Disgusting
You're about to go off. He took it too far
That's you about to I'm so tempted
I don't want to do this. He's tempted
Me you're gonna kill me off
Not kill it. I'm just gonna kick out the panel. It's not
Dad kick you off the island. Why would you? Yeah, why would you kick me off?
Because God he said so
I agree. I agree with him. I'm just kidding. Oh, yeah, I draw the line. So you know, there's a line has to be drawn
You have to change the subject. Yeah
Okay, all right. Let's change. Can we change the subject without taking me?
No, yeah, change the subject. Go ahead. Yeah, go ahead
up to you
Pick the new subject, but make it not sexually harassing. Yeah
Okay, how about that's why I came here so
Man, that's gay. Please. It's too gay for me and me and that's listening a lot. Okay. Sure. Sure like what she was talking about
I want her I'm gonna
I'm gonna pass it to her and be like, hey, what would you like to talk about? Would you like to talk about history?
I don't think I don't think that's a history is not like really that what our shows the shows about about like, you know
You're like talking about
Sometimes tears when I was the drama, but it's like not like history. That's kind of the Civil War
Yeah, I'm a war. Yeah, did you know anything about the war? She doesn't I
Lost his legs in the Civil War
You're like 300 years old
For a medical doctor, you love that joke.
Why are you making jokes like that?
It's kind of funny though.
It is funny.
There's morbid, isn't it?
I like her.
No, I like you again.
Got you I always joke about him being in a wheelchair and shit and one time I went too far and got he got silenced
I was talking about taking a hot dog for fourth of July and grounding it up and putting in his feeding tube to feed him
You think I'm the guy from that Metallica video one. I'm just laying
Who is saying that no arms no legs. I'm just a brain. I don't you know me
That's so fun
No, I'll meet you
Do you remember the other day whenever fucking I came up on what's the names and then fucking I was like
Oh, no, it's a
fucking
You know like a girl club and fuck it. Yeah. Yeah, you just came in there and you're like
It's looking girls club in here. I'm leaving and then you just left
You're funny
We were all laughing
That was hilarious
Yeah, I don't know why it's so fun harassing Goddy, but it is
I'm laughing God. I love it. It's okay. Go ahead. Get it out
Yeah, he likes it to see you you you go through a lot of stress. I do I need an outlet
We were talking about that this morning. We got it
Yes, you gotta let it out whether you punch someone in the face come up here and yell at someone
You guys were talking about this morning shit you guys fuck
You missed out
Dude literally man got he's one of my good friends man dude
He's so cool, man. He's really cool, dude
Yes
You guys are all cool. You guys are all cool in your own way all beautiful in your own way
And I like you all you better watch your mouth
Why would I say because I told you
I'll tell you something buddy. No, I told you something
No, didn't I know didn't I tell you something would you tell me you know Ziggy's mom watches the show, right?
Yeah, my mom's my mom's watching right now
That poor lady she loves she loves singing not see yeah signal. She loves signal a lot. Oh
That's one of her favorites
Oh, no, she kind of like sake sake and then she likes it this channel. Yeah, it's kind of crazy
Summer what do you know about Jamie Rose?
That 30 minutes to Jamie Rose or 20 or 20 second 20 minutes to Jamie Rose. What is it called? She's
Marty music. Oh 43 minutes. It's Marty's ex-girlfriend Marty music this
Love you knew him
His sirex is big troll
Marty yeah, oh my god, we're gonna get back to the
I used to do sports betting with Marty I just first thing I would win and he said he would send me money
He would send me money. He called me underdog. I always pick the underdog
And I would win. I was a good. I was a good
He's still alive guy again. He's still alive. Is that where you're laughing? What's wrong? He's alive, right?
I heard he was alive. Oh
Marty he always said you and you always said you would fake his death and then it's like now there's rumors. He's dead
Well, I don't know honey. He's not alive. Okay. We'll see we'll see we'll see
Honey
Why did you say you saw his body?
Are you are you doubting? Are you doubting me? Yes highly you're doubt you're doubting me right now
I can I just feel people are alive. I feel him in the air. He's not alive. Okay. All right
Most people think you're turning in him you're turning him into Tupac, okay
Most deaths are most deaths are faked. You know that you're turning him into Tupac on
Okay, oh, oh just Amy Rose. I caught oh, yeah
I wish I wish people were alive, you know, it's like I think to think that maybe
You are wishing that people were alive and they're not and you have to get with it. Okay. Well, it's okay
Hey, Jimmy, how are you?
Can you call me his underdog Lucky Charm?
Man again, and he already died of a heart attack. They get your ass together and fucking realize that fucking
Look at this shirt. Hold on. You like this shirt dogs make me feel less murder
Oh, I'm gonna get that shirt. Oh my god, you're gonna get that shirt. Oh, God. I want to get a towel
That's my real voice
Okay, um, yeah, I have you have okay
Okay, okay, I
Okay, it's your ass together
And everybody get their asses straight and let's go
Where are we going on this show? Where are we going? Where are we going?
Disneyland?
Yeah, I want to go to Disneyland. Oh my god. I'll say Disneyland, dude
Of course every fucking one minute is gonna feel like yeah
What the hell? Wait, you like Disneyland? I do. It's a magical it's a magical kingdom
We'll just like do some lie
Everyone's the biggest rapist place
I don't want to go there
Okay, anyway, okay, let's not go to Disneyland. Let's go to fucking a Disney world
Let's get a dolly world. It's called dolly wood don't dolly world dolly wood
Whatever
Play on the word Hollywood doll. I'm gonna go to the mario land
In your mother the Mario land in universal. Oh
Wait, the way she sounds. I want to take her to dolly wood
I'm gonna go to Graceland Graceland
Graceland
You and foil live near there don't you?
We might live near somewhere. Yeah, but there's not attractions there, dude
Like you can't like be rides and shit. If you're if you're there, you'll be the attraction
Okay, no, no, I know what you're doing. I'm not doing anything
Yeah, you know hard to I am out of things
What I'm saying what I'm saying is is that?
What the hell is the ride?
You can ride me what
Yeah, let's write each other in your horseback dollywood man. I want to get a dollywood
Okay, well, let's go come on rather train. Can you can you buy the
We're going if we're going to dollywood, I'm taking a plane. I'm definitely taking a plane. I think I can I think I can
Like I like her a lot
Come on rather train to to train yeah
Yeah, I do ever since I ever since I watch this documentary where I found out like that
There's this big railroad that went straight into the Auschwitz. I took thought differently about the railroads. Oh
In a show. Yeah, look at that. There's a railroad track that goes right inside of it. Oh
Yeah
You're always watching something negative like oh, I do. Yeah, I do too like it's German like they
So
You have to dwell on death
That's not necessarily negative or bad. It's like it's just what it's just like, you know, you learn from the history, right?
You learn from like her
You know, it doesn't repeat itself, right?
Yeah
Randy I like how I like her name
Brande you like you like this drink brandy. You don't like the name, right?
Right. Yeah, the alcohol just like the alcohol brandy. She's a fine girl
Yeah, like I want to like bang her and then like, you know hang out with you and like we go out to the bar
Yeah, how do I get involved in this?
What about Jim? Oh
She can you know, she's at home taking care of the kids
You know
Wow
I knew what you said
I like her you have a good you have a good host there
You want you want 49
I want 69 oh hell okay with it with it with it with Ziggy with Ziggy I want to do it with no no with me no please I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't want to I don't
Let's go if she's a is she available you have to ask her. Oh
No, no, I won't be I won't be touching her you that you that's just a distraction for you while I go to town
Oh, no, fuck. No, fuck. No, I'm not
Never mind
Straight up. Nope
Yes, Summer says she's gonna get the hell out of here
Okay, bye
Look at this. Oh, this is cute. This is this is a cute shirt. Look at this shirt. Look at this shirt. Look at this shirt.
It's a weirdo. Yeah, and you're weird. I'll keep you like yeah
Like if I might you I'd be like, oh my god
You're so yeah, you are weirdo. You are you are a weirdo. It's supposed to be you're
No, it needs an a it's weirdo. They're they're a weirdo. I think it didn't say weirdo. I thought it just said weird
No, no, you're a weirdo. It's like show it again
Okay
That's not it. Oh my god, I'm gonna get that for my son. Oh
You have a son I
Do oh
You're single you're single woman. Okay. No, no, I'm not single
You're not single. No, my boyfriend actually brought me in the chat
My boyfriend, my boyfriend, brought me in the chair, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my boyfriend, my
What is a song called no no no what you said that my boyfriend's back and what is that gonna be in trouble
It was weird huh, so no, I wouldn't weird you know, it's good that you guys know that song. That's pretty cool
Alex is back
Alex is back you got change that avatar because that could be an underage kid. Oh
Really funny, right?
You'll say that picture could be a 17 year old. It's not it's a 24
Who knows that for big their parents in this like you that's my missing daughter
Don't fuck with me you motherfucker. Shut up. Shut up. Oh really? Yes.
Hey, hey, hey, my boyfriend's back.
Always negative. Why is everybody attacking you all of them?
He's controversial. They perceive him as weak.
All controversy. Oh, you take your kindness for witness. Oh
You can't you can't do that. You can't do this kindness for weakness. I'm not I mean
Everybody takes your kindness for weakness. Well, that's it. That's that people's own peril because
There's if there was my weakness that the kindness would be the thing that like got me in trouble
It's never my kindness that got me in trouble. That was my woman. I was with the woman once like not
too long ago, you know, her name was Jan and
She is just
Hi, hi
Really, I want to be happy. Hi. Hi, and it just didn't work
You know what you want? Well, if you want to be happy, then you're not happy because it's like you want to be happy
You have to be happy
Exactly what you just want to be something you have to just be it. Just be it exactly
Precisely that's saying man. Holy shit
Go and try this for weakness
Fly fly a kite, you know
and Russia
That a fucking ditch
God
I think no, no, no, no, he wasn't meaning it like that
I'm gonna say it
a ditch
Oh, I can now you're now you know, you're gonna you're gonna double down on it. I meant them like that go cry the ditch
Don't cry
You better not get mad at me I was always told you
I'm sorry. I'm not get mad
You
If you get mad at me, I'm going to be
No, I don't like that one
You too much over the time you you you took out the ones I
Always find a violence
Yeah, what are they?
No, they're just they really just on team that I'm like trying to you're trying to get all this free stuff
They're always like, oh, you get like a always like free items if you like order anything is stupid never works
Yeah, there's they're really cheap. They're under $10 for a t-shirt. They just want you could even
Woman was even my woman listen listen listen even my woman was like
She was like I got teemured again. I'm like, why would you even team now?
Because I got good stuff on team. I like I like the all three things. I've bought so far
Yeah, well, she didn't
At least a Jordanic and wear a whole Timu outfit and look good in it
She got a whole her all over free on Timu and she looks great. My woman looks
Crazy stupid bat. Thank you. Where'd you get your clothes from?
Oh, I do high-end stuff and then I do like crappy stuff online to like Amazon and I'll mix it up
Where'd you go?
I go to the
Depending on what I'm gonna product. I have a voice
It's probably by the background. I have a couple
My god, it sounds like it's music. What's that music? I think it's the person that came on
Like it's like 50s music that is an X
Is it them that is an X? Oh, it's off. Perfect. Yeah, it's gone
I don't know what that was about
I don't know
It just means like a he's like not a legal citizen of another dimension
I'm not sure. Okay. Another dimension. Another dimension. Another dimension while I do it over time. Now that song's in my head. Every dimension. Every dimension. No, I know it wasn't you. I just wanted to say it was pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure. Pure
I
Told me he hates coming here
He never has to be here again
Don't make fun of it. No, no, but she says ruined ruined you ringed. What did you ringed?
He hates he hates being the butt of your jokes the cocking of Boyle basic. Oh
Okay, the JT sees it
I thought he was into that right well that was kind of like my no he did it. That was he did it just to make her happy
Oh, like he got cocked to please her. Yes. Oh shit. You said cocked. Oh shit
Yeah, but he's not into it. No. Oh shit. It's not like a Gary Tiffany's
It's not like that. Yeah, not like you're still you're never gonna lead dude. You're never
Which is that? Okay, got it. Hello. Who's that?
What's that noise? What's that noise? It's probably my stupid dogs fighting.
And there's like a women's voices. I hear like music and faces
Yes, is that you?
I'm muted
Who's there? Oh, that's why are you guys not talking? I'm muted
I was very I was very muted. Okay. All right
You guys are being safe, stupid right now.
I'm about to clear off the panel, Ziggy.
And you're going to be the first person.
You're going to be the first person I kick out, OK?
Why would I be the first one?
Because I was the only nice one.
Did they mistake your kindness for weakness?
They both saw a good place.
Don't you just hate that?
This is a big mistake because you don't know how kind I am.
You know, that happened to me once.
Well.
Yeah, once.
Just once.
Yeah.
Well.
Oh, you got penis picture up there.
Try everything because I was putting let me see the other people backstage. There's all these people backstage. Hello, President
President T Robert E. Hello, RFK. Are you hello? Oh, it's real
It's me and Donald we're both here. We wanted oh my god
We wanted to talk about health. Mr. Trump wanted to talk about anything really that's not the
This is not really about politics
I think you're straight. Thank you. I heard it's a wild card Wednesday
Which we have a lot of wild cards, right? Yeah
The jokers. Yes, the jokers. It's the president. I'm a big fan. Thank you. I appreciate it
It's an honor sir. It's an honor
Are we afraid to put this guy on screen so what's going on? Oh, yeah, I mean, there's there's Trump. There's Alex
I mean, I think there's a lot of people here. Hold on
There you go. Hello. I mean, there's only two people who are heads of government and I think they're probably going to take priority over
Anyone else? No, it's not a political show and I didn't vote for either of you
There's no politics. That's not political. We're just going to talk about how you can be healthy and how we can improve our
Please
Don't touch my coke. Don't touch my coke zero
I'm not gonna. I'm not we're not gonna touch your coke zero, but we're gonna get rid of any artificial flavors and artificial
Not too long ago actually
Getting all the other things out of the coke right we're gonna put only the cane sugar back into the
And that's actually what we wanted to talk about, right?
Well, there's a lot of people that don't know that you can color things with natural substitutes.
You don't have to use red 40 or yellow 4 or any of these coloring agents.
You can use things like cockroach sperm or you can use things like pig brains.
And they do the same thing.
Well, thank you guys.
Guys, this is so funny.
I mean, it's really, really funny.
It is so funny, but okay.
Wait, wait, wait.
What's wrong with the stat tire?
It's not political.
Yeah
More like Gilbert Godfried
I haven't seen that before
he's just uh he's doing a bad imitation it's called
rebrand water as coke no no the trump one's an ai and i'm saying that's doing that in real time i
don't know it's not an ai it's a real person the trump no no no that's the fucking way
Oh, that's the guy. What would you say something like that? You know what?
I think this is a guy that has brain worms. I think it's somebody who needs to have his brain checked for worms
If you put this put the president on screen. Hey, Mr. Mr. President. What's the deal with the Epstein list?
What's going on there? I'm so sick of this
I thought this wasn't a political show, it's not it's not guys
Because you know who's on the list, you know who's on the list the top dogs on that list, you know
Can you can you do a reading for Bobby? I think he wants a reading done
Okay, Bobby would
If you could do a tarot reading I actually I remember I was in New Orleans and I was
there was somebody in New Orleans who gave me a reading
Yeah, give the president a reading, bro, before he fucking plays fighting
Holy shit, Alex just said
RFK was never the president
Get the fuck up, yo, Mr. President, suck my dick
Excuse me?
Hey, hey, hey
Good luck, will ya?
No, the truck is definitely an AI voice. The committee is not. I don't that's not AI. Come on
Well, I don't think you know anything about anything. I think you're just saying thanks, and I don't think
That was Kenny doing
But that's okay
People have thought this before they think we're the same person because I guess we aligned so well is that right mr. President?
We aligned very I know
Here's the microphone. Okay. We got it. We got a show that we're not the same person go ahead and talk
We can say whatever together at the same time
23 minutes of not reading anything have you even been reading anything I mean you have all these people on here
Have you read every single person?
I've been ready anybody tonight, but it's like we're you know, it's a wild card evening. We're gonna see what comes up, right?
Okay, well, what's gonna come up for Bobby? Okay, we run a car for Bobby
Oh, yeah, I mean, we got it if you want to talk about reading books
I have a book called the real Anthony Fauci
Don't mention that person. Okay. Oh, excuse me. Well, if you read this book about the real so-and-so
I'm not gonna say his name, but if you if you read about it
There's a lot of things about that I go into about how HIV and AIDS are actually
Okay, let's not talk about it, let's not talk about it
Well, that's not, I'm talking, this is health
It's very serious, it's very controversial
It's very controversial, let's stop
No, I think this is health, I think we're talking about red 40 in the red 80
No, we're talking about it
It's called silence, silence
You want to keep silence? Okay, God
You sound like you eat a lot of burritos
Is that a man?
Who
I don't know
A lot of studies on that on on on their putting the sports
Only you would say that bro
I got a book called about me shut up. Oh fuck up man. You're both retarded. You
White House making bad policy decisions, and we just bought my rent two weeks ago. Everyone forgot about that
I don't think you're giving me any credit for getting artificial flavors out of our food supply.
Well, we found the Democrat ladies and gentlemen.
I appreciate it.
We don't have any artificial flavors or artificial dyes as of 2,233.
Think of it.
We're making Pop Tarts great again.
Oh my God.
We're going to have healthier Pop Tarts.
We're going to have healthier Gatorades.
We're going to have healthier.
The process jumped.
This is very important to me. I want to get into it. When you feed your children apple jacks
Now you're going to be able to feed your children apple jacks without red 40 and what that does is that changes their entire
development
Man like my abs
Really good
It's true. Well, I don't know where the hell Bobby just went. You should have done a reading
I guess you just wasted another hour and a half
Listen Roberto Roberto Clemente shut up. I'm talking to Trumpy
Let me ask you a question
Excuse me kids the UNF steam have fun with
Like Alice was that somebody who does not that somebody who does not follow the food pyramid only interacts with human beings over you
You know, I like what you're doing candy, but why'd you kill that bear?
Like that years. Well, I can explain that whole story has been misrepresented
and and has been because i was in the park and i i i remember i was driving and i ran over a baby bear
and it was not on purpose it was very late and the only reasonable thing for me is not to waste
the carcass because there's a lot of people who they waste the carcass so it's true i tied them to
I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it,
Low IQ what's this whole thing about grabbing them by the put grabbing them by the pussy your man
The only question is Rosie O'Donnell and stormy dandles, okay
Actually
Alright, get Bobby back in here. What's going on? Why is Bobby not here?
What's going on?
What the hell? I thought you were going to give him a nice opinion.
Because I'm like the second or third in line if something happens to Mr. Trump to be president.
It's like 10.
Hey, hey, hey. Can you stop talking about politics, please?
I know you're a politician, but please stop talking about politics.
No, I didn't think it was political to say that going for a run and not consuming red
Gatorade is good for you.
Don't you shouldn't be drinking anything like you need to calm the hell down so many fine. I'm fine
But uh, yeah
Guys red number two has been hilarious. It's been illegal since nineteen like seventy-eight or whatever
No, I'm talking about red number 40. This guy doesn't listen donald. He doesn't listen
That's the new one that causes the rage the rage problems that cause people to rage out
Well, I've never raged out in my entire life. I've always been very calm and very serene
are you drinking the Gatorade though you're not drinking the red no I would never I would never touch
this stuff I think if we made every Gatorade flavor yellow I think it would solve a lot of problems
how about just like I think so I'd rather drink you know rather than Gatorade how would you just
drink like you know pee
Well, I was gonna say drinking your own piss has actually been proven in studies
I have I have several studies from the University of Yale
Drinking your own piss can actually be really good for your
Mr. President you can allude to this but it's it's better to have someone else's pee
Yeah, that's what I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was
I'm gonna do a reading fail.
They don't sleep.
Okay, I don't...
Yeah.
I'll do a joke reading.
They go on reading.
Because you guys are jokes.
I'll do a joke reading, but I won't...
I think that's...
I think again, you're just denying.
You're denying your health.
You're not a true reader. I only want to drink Ziggy's pee. Okay. It's a mess of Ziggy
What makes Ziggy so damn special because he drinks all he drinks is the Gatorade
Red Gatorade and then it will like I'll be able to drink it
The only drinks Gatorade probably makes his piss taste even worse. Oh my god. I'll be disrespectful. I'm asking him a question
It was it a question
My tablet sleepy, I'm just looking in the conversation, okay?
Our Kelly P. Oh, I'm talking to the chat. Don't worry. So I'd argue in PD. You look the same all blacks look the same
That's not true. Come on. So look at look at look at Bill Cosby
All right, he's playing he's playing subway surface right now. He's got a problem. Oh, there we go
Now you're gonna get to the reading three hours and 31 minutes later
I don't I don't want to go off topic here, mr. President, but he did bring up Bill Cosby and he's actually an old friend of mine
We used to yeah
I have a pet aardvark that I remember I had him over and we played a pet aardvark at my house
And Bill Cosby is a very nice man and he exactly as he is on the show
It's funny
We love
The Lex was not too happy
We need to get rid of the words that are in front of the word on work because
They've added words to the dictionary that made our first word word in the dictionary. No, but it's before it
I would know you didn't tell me okay so I don't want to hear I don't want to hear Donald's
what is it called tarot reading I want to hear what it what it is oh gosh my neck
He's been waiting his whole life for this damn reading actually he had to go
Under a little bit of a problem. I don't know if you know that.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Okay, why did you leave the Baron and send him apart?
I already explained that story, but I can explain it again.
Hey, I ran over a baby bear.
It was completely an accident.
And then I strapped him to the top of my car
and drove him across state lines.
But there's a whole there's a whole story to that
because I don't believe in wasting carcasses.
What's something is.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
The Kennedy's are still cursed since the Macbeth days, right?
I would just stay away from the libraries, observatories, you know, circular parking
lots, any place with like a, you know, some place over your head where you can, like,
a sniper can be hidden.
Stay with the snipers.
Those Kennedy's.
Kennedys had the worst luck around snipers right are you gonna read it's been three hours 34. Yes, okay for you
For Bobby's gone, I kicked him out of the chat. Why did you get him back?
Okay, he's being okay, I'll be good. I'll be quiet. I won't talk about the bear that I hit in Central Park and
to not waste his carcass i tied him to the top of the car i won't talk about it okay okay don't
please please that's enough of the story i mean it's like really i mean that that
i was a summer asked about it and i thought i don't know what she looks like my cat lol i'm sorry
There are studies at Harvard that actually concluded eating cats is actually not the
worst thing that you could do.
It does lower blood pressure.
It's not cats. Okay. It's a very low
In charge rft
My ex-girlfriend said I didn't need enough cats
Yeah, okay well
I don't know
Yeah, okay Rfk like I'm just feeling you have the cards actually
I don't think you have the cards right now to be honest with you
I have the car. I have the cards, but do you want me to take this seriously?
Right now. I do
Okay, don't mean to do a reading. I'll do I'll do a reading but it's not gonna be like for your fictional character
I take it seriously, so it will be for your like actual self and so if it read
Don't just don't pretend
I'll do a very short
36 minutes and we're still trying to figure this out. Okay. Okay. Okay. I got it. Okay
Okay, okay
Okay, so there's somebody okay, so so there is somebody spying on you right now, but you are like really like there's somebody watching
It's like the pages swords a little kid a little like a right yeah
It's pages swords and the pages swords spy the spy of the terror deck. They're always
probably an air sign
like
Watching watching you or maybe you are because you're coming up as the
Want which is like a very almost pretty close probably
Emperor like energies. It's a fun. It's a king of the fire science
That's too far from the Disney animated film Aladdin. It's too far. Yeah, I know, but it's like he's the king of wands
Okay, and then we have the only understand. Okay. Yes. Okay, then but then we also have
The six of cups and this is like medicine reverse. Okay, so this is like some kind of bad memories of
The past like you're you're focusing on like some kind of bad thing that happened or that there's some kind of bad memory
but
Also, we have this aid of coins. Okay, so this aid of coins is like, you know
Really protecting what you have. Okay, so just just because there's maybe some tiny hyenas. See that hyenas is blanking
So they're even I on things so just just watch out. Okay, so there you go Disney. I
Do like Disney I do like and you know not
That reminds me of a law that just passed my desk
We're gonna actually make it illegal to watch Disney films past the age of 20
Well, I haven't really watched these films since I was you know young, but I loved the little mermaid
I loved a beast Aladdin. I don't have to switch the cards. It's a villains deck. It's a very cool deck, you know
It's like I think I mean, I I don't want to speak for him, but I think I think Donald is a hero
Of what?
Where
Every hero how how people say sir. You're a great guy. You're a hero
They say actually they say sir you have the hottest country in the entire world right now
You have the hottest country. That's because you're the king. They say sir
In your cards you pulled out a card it said I was the king so yeah, but you know, that's the emperor speech
you know what you said to tell him what you said to rocket man
what did you say to rocket man oh who's rocket man you don't want to know who is it
rocket man elton john just to figure that one out okay oh hold on what are you chatting or
you wouldn't have been a rocket right no you're talking about kim okay kim
For I forgot I forgot a bit, but I said you don't know you don't know I'm pretty sure I'm
Reading
I mean that was the reading I have some advice for you though some some advice for RFK
Was that for Bobby was that for me?
But I was I was hardly paying attention. I need to know it's okay. I you know, okay, it's okay
There's the moon and so that kind of says you weren't paying attention
There was like, you know, there's something's not gonna be clear about that
But it's like, you know, it will become clear in time. I just just feel like, you know, it'll all make sense
Okay, so rocket man looks like a mini man's okay
Trump we need to cancel happy meals. It's too gay. We need America straight again
Well, we have unhappy meals or we're called sad meals now. I mean, I don't know
I can't think of a better time to bring this up, but we are as of today no longer paying for
Uh, school lunches for kids. We're we're announcing that today, and I think it's a very strong move. Wonderful. Wonderful. I mean
We are gonna keep offering breakfasts, but not dinners
Well, they don't have breakfast
They don't have dinner in school. Yeah, excuse me. Thank you. So I think I think I think that's I think that's a
misrepresentation of the facts
Excuse me ladies
Listen, so we had a little bit of a problem in the schools, right with the school lunches
These kids they come from you know all over the world, right?
And they would come into the classroom with a dead puppy. It was oh my god
just
Guys guys dead dead puppies is not a dead puppies is not a very popular top
Guys you don't mess with dogs
Dogs if a dog dies
He's been hoping the whole family can be right down the dog
My grandson says it was abandoned the early 2000s called the sick puppies and he says that they rocked
Does that does anybody know anything about me wait never heard of them?
See like can I get a reading please? Can you would see you would like
Excuse me Pat. It's been three hours 41 minutes in
47 that's a good number
Right, we're rating the great one great one one in a minute
While he's doing his turret while he's getting his terrets together
I can take each of your blood tests and I can tell you when you're going to die
Oh, I don't I don't want to know that's not me
That's something I mean
No, it's science. It's it's about I there was a study from the University of Alabama that actually went into that
No, I actually want a reading like, you know, I'm doing it right now. I'm looking at right now
Okay, all right, well, okay
So I can you ever give you kiddies palm assages. Why do women?
Love must they love massage. They had to go from the tarot of palm assages for you kitty like palm
Woman she won. Hey Ziggy
Ziggy, okay, I got your reading for you. Okay, so we got first of all we have the devil, but the devil's in reverse
Oh, this is so Ziggy this is coming out of some kind of
Wow best for laughs the best for laughs
I don't know he's I don't know what he's the devil in some Disney movie. I don't know if it's not
I don't know if it's Hades or what but I don't think so. Okay, everybody's like no everybody's interrupting
Hey, no one interrupted. I'm just saying this is a being in reverse the devil in reverse
It could mean that you're getting out of some kind of
Negative or like lower situation. It's just having to do with the material world. How do you mean lower situation? Okay?
You're getting closer
The devil is about the earth, right? It's like the devil is and about I always understood the devil as the
Covid-19 vaccine. Okay. Okay. No, no, please don't mention that
Okay, but okay, but it looks like it looks like you've come out of like some kind of imbalance
You've got you've got these you got these two these two energies bouncy that they're working together
little pattern right so the so the temperate temperance you got the balance back and so you've
found some balance in your life um but you're also uh there's something like there's somebody
there's somebody you want to give a gift or something to you're not doing it like there's
yeah you and i you you and i aren't balancing very good well i don't know i don't think i think
it's probably a woman because i do see this true love card no well no that's the thing that's your
Well, there's I mean, there's a third part in the third party. So there's a jealous person
A little bitch, yeah
Because I think you can't even board a deal. I mean that's it. I mean, that's the reason for cards for cards very fast. Okay, there you go
There you go. See we figured it out
Now why is this guy yacking who is that?
Who? RFK or Trump?
I don't know.
Excuse me?
So I would call it yakking.
I have a laryngeitis.
It makes me speak very strangely, but I wouldn't say it was yakking.
You sound like Gilbert Godfrey
Shocker I'm very shocked
I mean we went to Disney World together and we were really good friends
With Walt Disney, everybody, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with Walt Disney, with
Well, I don't think it was a misogynist.
Check the flight log, check the flight log.
I'm not on the flight log, okay?
I was not.
Mr. Trump, have you asked me,
psych is getting very cold.
We're going to change the subject right now,
if you care about psychies panel.
End of story.
New subject.
Excuse me.
Don't ever say that name up here again.
And you're laughing a little too much, brother.
Shut the fuck up.
Talk about it anything else from now on that
McQueen is certainly acting like a queen I'll tell you that right now
Alex is all of a sudden
I keep shut them all up hit him with a stone or
All video
That can take a shit taking down an art seems like more of a character
University of Vermont and they found that gas station
You're on it look at my profile picture
I